<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Oliver's Personal Podcast</title>
    <link>http://oops.hopto.org:9090/oliver/publicprofile</link>
    <description>I publish interesting things !!!</description>
    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator> </generator>
    <language>es-ES</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:30:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <itunes:author>oliver</itunes:author>
    <managingEditor>oliver.barreto.online@gmail.com (oliver)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 10:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <itunes:category text="News"/>
    <itunes:image href="https://github.com/oliverbarreto/PersonalPodcast/raw/main/site-logo-1400x1400.png"/>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>oliver</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>oliver.barreto.online@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/oliverbarreto/PersonalPodcast/main/oliver_feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>ÁREA 51 #CuartoMilenio - Canal Iker Jiménez</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Los secretos del Área 51, al descubierto

Iker Jiménez y Carmen Porter acaban de regresar de la famosa Área 51. Se trata de un destacamento remoto controlado por la base aérea de Edwards, en el sur del estado de Nevada (Estados Unidos).

Se desconoce el objetivo principal de esta base, aunque lo más probable es que en ella se estén llevando a cabo proyectos de investigación y desarrollo con sistemas de armamento avanzados. Sin embargo, debido al secretismo que la envuelve, son muchas las teorías conspiratorias en torno los objetos volantes no identificados y el Área 51. Iker, Carmen, el escritor Javier Sierra y el periodista Enrique de Vicente intentarán dar respuesta a muchas de las interrogantes que envuelven a este enclave.

💬 | Cuarto Milenio: programas completos disponibles en Cuatro y Mitele.
→   https://www.cuatro.com/cuarto-milenio/alacarta/
→   https://www.mitele.es/programas-tv/cuarto-milenio/]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.rm-1B64DD-Y</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/rm-1B64DD-Y.m4a" length="74865062" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 10:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/rm-1B64DD-Y/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>0</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Canal Iker Jiménez published on Wednesday, February  7 2024 at 03:05:09</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady Talks Taking On His Newest Challenge &amp; Mahomes GOAT Comparisons | Full Interview - The Pat McAfee Show</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Welcome to The Pat McAfee Show LIVE from Noon-3PM EST Mon-Fri. You can also find us live on ESPN, ESPN+, &amp; TikTok!

Become a #McAfeeMafia member! https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCxcTeAKWJca6XyJ37_ZoKIQ/join

SUBSCRIBE:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCxcTeAKWJca6XyJ37_ZoKIQ?sub_confirmation=1

MERCH: https://store.patmcafeeshow.com

Subscribe to the Pat McAfee Show(s)!
 @Hammer Dahn  
 @Thats Hockey Talk  
 @The Pod  
 @The Pat McAfee Show  
   
MERCH: https://store.patmcafeeshow.com
SPONSOR THE SHOW: https://www.patmcafeeshow.com/partnerships

#PatMcAfee #NFL]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.jx-ana5f428</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/jx-ana5f428.m4a" length="30417869" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/jx-ana5f428/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>1</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by The Pat McAfee Show published on Tuesday, January 30 2024 at 21:30:08</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>¿Cómo convertirse en HACKER? | Con @s4vitar 🔴 HackerLIVE#29 - MoureDev by Brais Moure</title>
      <description><![CDATA[¿Quieres aprender ciberseguridad y convertirte en hacker? 
S4vitar, hacker y divulgador, nos habla sobre hacking ético, ciberseguridad, y cómo podemos llegar a seguir sus pasos.

► SIGUE A S4VITAR:
• @s4vitar 
• https://twitch.tv/s4vitaar
• https://twitter.com/S4vitar

🔗  Redes y enlaces de interés: https://moure.dev
👾  Discord: https://mouredev.com/discord
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
🕹  Twitch: https://twitch.tv/mouredev (directos de Lunes a Viernes)
🐦  Twitter: https://twitter.com/mouredev
📷  Instagram: https://instagram.com/mouredev
🎶  TikTok: https://tiktok.com/@mouredev
📩  Newsletter: http://newsletter.mouredev.com
👕  Merchandising: https://tienda.mouredev.com
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
🔔  SUSCRÍBETE Y ACTIVA LA CAMPANA: https://goo.gl/afPz3g
🏆  COLABORA CON EL CANAL: https://www.youtube.com/mouredevapps/join
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
💻  MI EQUIPO/SETUP:
https://mouredev.com/setup
https://www.amazon.es/shop/mouredev
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
🎓  CURSO COMPLETO iOS 15 y Swift 5.5  DESDE CERO:
https://www.udemy.com/course/swift_ios
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
⏳  TWITIMER, LA APP PARA APRENDER PROGRAMACIÓN DE LA COMUNIDAD:
https://twitimer.com
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
⭐️  DESCUENTOS Y COLABORADORES:
• Elgato: https://e.lga.to/MoureDev
• Macnificos: https://macnificos.com/tienda/?tt=31560_12_407642_&amp;r=%2F
• Hostinger: https://hostinger.com/mouredev (Cupón &quot;MOUREDEV&quot; descuento 7%)
• MacPaw: https://macpaw.audw.net/c/2550109/94160/1733
• ClickUp: https://clickup.com?fp_ref=brais66&amp;promo=MOUREDEV
• GitKraken: https://www.gitkraken.com/invite/cZWhJq1v
• NordVPN: https://nordvpn.org/mouredev
• CodelyTV Pro: https://codely.tv/pro/mouredev 

#Hacker #Ciberseguridad #HackerLive]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.79JygZ7DUqw</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/79JygZ7DUqw.m4a" length="158175987" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 18:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/79JygZ7DUqw/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>2</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by MoureDev by Brais Moure published on Wednesday, October  6 2021 at 19:00:03</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck - Summarized by the Author - Mark Manson</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck - Author’s Summary

This is the official summary of the mega-bestseller &#x27;The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck: A Counterintuitive Approach to Living a Good Life&#x27; by me, Mark Manson. See below for chapter time codes.

Intro: 00:00
Chapter 1: DON&#x27;T TRY 02:43
Chapter 2: HAPPINESS IS A PROBLEM 06:46 
Chapter 3: YOU ARE NOT SPECIAL 11:03
Chapter 4: THE VALUE OF SUFFERING 15:03
Chapter 5: YOU ARE ALWAYS CHOOSING 18:19
Chapter 6: YOU&#x27;RE WRONG ABOUT EVERYTHING (BUT SO AM I) 23:05
Chapter 7: FAILURE IS THE WAY FORWARD 27:31
Chapter 8: THE IMPORTANCE OF SAYING NO 30:33
Chapter 9: AND THEN YOU DIE... 33:41

Like. Share. Comment. Subscribe. You know the drill.

Everything is Fucked: A Book About Hope Official Summary here: https://youtu.be/fEk5dhbNU70

—

Sign up for my newsletter to receive three actionable pieces of advice each week that could change your life - free sign up here: http://bit.ly/3JRg3NX

If you are not already a member of my premium membership, get access to my courses and exclusive writing here: http://bit.ly/3LwHWfi

I am Mark Manson, 3x #1 NY Times bestselling author of:

The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck - https://mrk.mn/3svfxcu
Everything Is F*cked: A Book About Hope - https://mrk.mn/2RNxVAD

I share other types of content to make you a less awful human in these places:

https://instagram.com/markmanson/
https://twitter.com/IAmMarkManson
https://facebook.com/Markmansonnet/
https://linkedin.com/in/markmanson/
https://www.tiktok.com/@iammarkmanson

Thanks for watching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.lz8sUiXAnbs</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/lz8sUiXAnbs.m4a" length="36650639" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 10:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/lz8sUiXAnbs/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>3</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Mark Manson published on Thursday, March  4 2021 at 20:13:55</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 6 Habits Of HIGHLY EFFECTIVE People You Can Copy! (CHANGE EVERYTHING) | Brendon Burchard - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Build IRONCLAD discipline in this free workshop: https://bit.ly/3pMVl6J

On Today&#x27;s Episode: 

It’s easy to admire people that have reached extraordinary levels of success, it’s hard to imagine what it takes to get there. Passing off someone’s excellence and success as unattainable for ourselves is a b.s. and it’s not what we’re about at Impact Theory. 

Your beliefs are malleable and what you believe about yourself matters. How you decide to live your life and show today matters also and if you’re not happy with the way you show up or how you’re living your life then do something about it.

Brendon Burchard is one of the world’s leading high performance coaches that has impacted and trained millions of people globally. His online personal growth platform is dedicated to teaching people how to bring the joy, live with intention, love the life you live, and matter to yourself and others everyday because you show up to go all-in on whatever you decide.

You’ve heard what it takes to be successful, but very few people share how to get beyond passion and shoot for obsession to attain insane levels of success, but today we are, so let’s go.

SHOW NOTES:

0:00 | Introduction to Brendon Burchard
2:22 | Generate the Energy You Want
10:15 | Raise Necessity with Obsession
15:51 | These 2 Things BUILD Your Identity
26:33 | Build These Skills Achieve More
35:47 | Honor the Struggle to Win

QUOTES:

“If you’re not a fun person when you&#x27;re broke, you’re not going to be that much more fun when you’re rich.” [4:00]

“High performers are generating the energy, and that means the mental, emotional and physical energy, that they feel is necessary to serve with excellence in a certain situation.” [9:45]

“People don’t want to exude that much passion which becomes obsession because they’re fearful of their obsessions.” [12:36] 

“If no one thinks you’re crazy you’re not yet operating to the outer limits of your potential.” [13:43]

“Being obsessed about something that gives you no feedback is not scary, being obsessed about something, like trying to make an impact in the world you’re going to get feedback.” [14:39]

“If you want to win, your identity has to be tied into that thing in which you are trying to succeed at and give to, and that takes a lot of guts to ut yourself all in…” [18:32]

“This is who I’m going to be and I’m going to build into that, and it is necessary for me to become that person.” [26:22]

“High performers are consistently seeking clarity in ‘who do I want to be?’ [...] in every situation.” [31:15]

“I don’t want a friction free life, [...] The journey to greatness begins the moment that our deep desires for comfort and for ease are overpowered by our desires to connect and contribute.”  [40:08]

“Determine what the questions at the end of your life are going to be.” [42:49]

Follow Brendon Burchard:
Website: https://brendon.com/ 
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brendonburchard/ 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/brendonburchardfan 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/BrendonBurchard 
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/user/BrendonBurchard]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.Q-xVb3V_zqI</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/Q-xVb3V_zqI.m4a" length="43989194" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/Q-xVb3V_zqI/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>4</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Tuesday, August 30 2022 at 13:00:25</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEGATHREAT: Why AI Is So Dangerous &amp; How It Could Destroy Humanity | Mo Gawdat - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Listen to Impact Theory on Amazon Music: https://music.amazon.com/podcasts/9e0db1b9-b46c-4e50-a9c5-add34b0ffe00/impact-theory-with-tom-bilyeu?ref=dm_sh_nzgPULGEOD2WFqOCd38MsElYP

Restart Your Life in 7 Days: http://bit.ly/42KM8OR

After reading Mo Gawdat’s book, Scary Smart, I knew right away this conversation was a must. As I think about AI’s capabilities – the good, the bad and possibly terrifying, I realize how serious this moment is in history for humanity.

Mo Gawdat is the former chief business officer for Google X and has built a monumental career in the tech industry working with the biggest names to reshape and reimagine the world as we know it. From IBM to Microsoft, Mo has lived at the cutting edge of technology and has taken a strong stance that AI is a bigger threat to humanity than global warming.

The AI dilemma is reshaping our future whether you’re in favor of it or not. The question is, are we even close to being prepared for humanity’s collision with artificial intelligence?

Strap in for the ride, we’re diving headfirst into this conversation and uncovering the alarming truth about how vulnerable we actually are and what that means for the next decade ahead.

QUOTES:

“It really is about a point of no return. Where if we cross that point of no return we have very little chance to bring the genie back into the bottle.”

“There is no shutting down AI, there is no reversing it, there is no stopping development of it.”

“We’ve never created a nuclear weapon that can create nuclear weapons.”

“The growth on the next chip in your phone is going to be a million times more than the computer that put people on the moon.”

“When we ask computers to communicate, at first they communicate like we tell them, but if they&#x27;re intelligent enough, they&#x27;ll start to say, ‘that&#x27;s too slow.’”

“One of our better scenarios, believe it or not, is that AI ignores us altogether.”

“Technology today can influence one human at a time.”


Follow Mo Gawdat:
Website: https://www.mogawdat.com/ 
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCilMYYyoot7vhLn4Tinzmmg 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/mgawdat 
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/mo_gawdat/]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.itY6VWpdECc</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/itY6VWpdECc.m4a" length="173357430" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/itY6VWpdECc/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>5</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Tuesday, June 20 2023 at 13:00:27</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Waking Up At 3:30 am Everyday Will CHANGE YOUR LIFE (Try This For 7 Days!) | Tom Bilyeu - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Click here to download your FREE guide to 100x YOUR EFFICIENCY IN 10 EASY STEPS: https://bit.ly/3F8qOJL

Build IRONCLAD discipline in this FREE workshop: https://bit.ly/3RUnYux

On Today&#x27;s Episode:

Do you enjoy the snooze alarm game? A lot of people you know including yourself do. It’s kind of fun but mostly torture. For 30 to 60 minutes, depending on your level of expertise, you get to see how many times you will hit the snooze button and sleep in 5 or 10 minute intervals before having to jump out of bed and mad dash through the morning to get ready. 

Every day, you wake up exhausted, you don’t get to the most important thing you told yourself the night before you would do first thing in the morning, your energy is low before noon and by 3 PM you’re begging yourself for a nap.

The key to breaking this cycle to start waking up at the time you want and need to is having the habits and routines built in place that make you so efficient that success becomes inevitable.

You don’t have to struggle every morning to get up early, you don’t need to set an alarm every night before bed to get up in the morning on time, and you don’t have to suffer through your days forever tired.

This is the video you need to hear to truly understand, how hardcore is hardcore for Tom Bilyeu when it comes to being the founder of a billion dollar company?

A few simple strategies you can start with right now are:

Go to bed same time (every day)
Do not use an alarm
Sleep as much as you need (it’s that important)

QUOTES:

“Your life will change forever the moment you decide to go to us early and really attack your day.”

“The snooze alarm says that you’ve not gotten control of your evenings.”

“You don’t need time to unwind, you are creating a torture cycle for yourself. You need a method for shutting your brain off.”

“I define truth as the thing that most efficiently moves you towards your goal.”

“My life is an exact reflection of my choices and that I made my day a little bit worst by not doing what I said I was going to do.”

“Boredom kills more dreams than failure I promise you.”

Follow Tom Bilyeu:
Website: https://impacttheory.com/ 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/TomBilyeu 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/tombilyeu]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.9RXdAdjy0_o</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/9RXdAdjy0_o.m4a" length="93113761" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/9RXdAdjy0_o/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>6</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Saturday, March 18 2023 at 13:00:06</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chat GPT, The FUTURE Of AI And Is It The End Of Human Civilization? | Tom Bilyeu - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Click here to download your FREE guide to 100x YOUR EFFICIENCY IN 10 EASY STEPS: https://bit.ly/3F8qOJL

Chat GPT AI went from 0 to over 100Million users in less than 2 months. AI is super fucking dangerous, but it’s inevitable, will make our lives better, and you should CAREFULLY love it. 

Is AI dangerous? Next to thermonuclear war and an asteroid strike, I’d say it’s the most radically dangerous threat that we face as a species. Buuuuut I’m still super excited. And by the end of this video you will be too.

If you’re terrified of AI right now, you’re rational. If you’re not at least worried it will take a wrong turn into James Cameron territory, you’re not paying attention. To paraphrase Elon Musk, the human endeavor to create AI could be the first step towards a technological utopia or a demon summoning circle. It’s not clear which way it will go. But one thing is for sure, we will not control it. And he’s right, but the truth is, the genie is out of the bottle, and we’re going to have to deal with it.  

For the most part our insatiable drive for progress is awesome. The modern world really is a miracle. We have buses that fly for the love of god. And if people like Eric Weinstein are correct, our thirst for progress will lead us to building technology that doesn’t just allow us to fly around the world, it will give us the ability to manipulate time and space itself - propelling us well beyond our solar system at faster than light speeds. 


I fear it will be a bit of both.

AI, which simply stands for Artificial Intelligence, is getting smart. Really smart. And AI doesn’t have to outsmart us by much to completely dominate us. Let me give you an example for scale: A moron is technically someone with an IQ of about 70. The average IQ in the US is 98. Einstein was estimated to be 160. And according to the Guiness book of World Records, the highest IQ ever recorded came in at a whopping 210. That means that a super genius is only 3 times smarter than a moron. But Einstein, who was actually only 2.3 times smarter than a moron, had insights that gave birth to nuclear power and nuclear bombs, not to mention lasers, GPS, and a whole lot more. Said another way, a little intelligence goes a loooooooong way. 

Nuclear warheads are scary enough, but AI isn’t going to be a little smarter than Einstein, it’s going to be a LOT smarter. Not 5 times smarter or 10 times or even 10,000 times smarter. We’re talking millions of times smarter. 

Despite the reality of all the bad stuff that’s coming, here are three traps we must avoid.
1. Burying our heads in the sand. 
2. Panicking. 
3. Trying to abolish AI.

Panicking is the same as actively taking your own intelligence offline. When you panic, blood leaves your prefrontal cortex, which is the seat of high level cognition. Therefore it actually makes you dumber. And in the face of artificial super intelligence that strikes me as a very bad idea. 

This is going to be the bleakest thing that I say today, but if we’re going to walk a wise path forward, we’ve got to face all of this. And, as they say, it’s darkest right before dawn, which I promise is coming. But first, here’s the reality you will instantly know to be true - when humans find powerful things we use them. 

Because AI as a weapon is a zero sum game. If only one nation develops it, it will be winner take all. And no one can risk an adversary getting Artificial Super Intelligence while they sit around entering funny prompts into ChatGPT. 

In the short term you need to do three things:

1. Reframe your thinking around AI. Don’t see it as the enemy. See it as a tool. You’re not going to be replaced by AI, at least not yet. You’re going to be replaced by a human using AI. Be the human that replaces others.
2. Figure out how AI is going to disrupt you. Face it head on. Don’t run. Don’t hide. Identify your vulnerabilities and shore up your skill set.
3. Identify all of the AI tools that are relevant to you and master them. Learn absolutely everything you can.

Remember, this is the very beginning of a very aggressive revolution. Moving quickly gives you advantages.

First of all, let me acknowledge that I’m a pundit here, not an expert. While we’re working feverishly to integrate AI into our company’s workflow, I’m not the guy who can tell you how AI works under the hood. So what follows will be me thinking out loud based on what I’ve learned from the experts in my attempts to use AI in both my daily life and the daily operations of my company.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.F2LeyULGF2Q</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/F2LeyULGF2Q.m4a" length="16948387" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/F2LeyULGF2Q/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>7</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Wednesday, March 15 2023 at 23:13:01</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIEMPOS DECISIVOS: EL FINAL DEL PRINCIPIO - Vlog de Marc Vidal - Marc Vidal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[La historia del dinero, sus usos y sus bancos. Te explico la situación actual y te dejo dos intervenciones en televisión. Ha empezado la fase final del principio. A partir de ahora se desarrollará todo. Esta es la situación actual en la que nos encontramos, sin un patrón establecido y con sistemas monetarios que varían de un país a otro. Y ahora, han decidido emitir CDBCs para que no puedas quejarte.  Como te digo, os dejo con dos vídeos de esta semana. Uno en Horizonte y otro en El Cascabel. De los pocos sitios que me permiten ir. Ya sabes… Espero que os guste. Seguiré subiendo material como pueda aunque me voy unos días con la familia a descansar en esta semana santa. Leed mucho, descansad y comed bien. Nos vemos pronto, os dejo con estas dos intervenciones]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.Of5d57GLAiY</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/Of5d57GLAiY.m4a" length="30397215" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 17:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/Of5d57GLAiY/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>8</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Marc Vidal published on Saturday, April  1 2023 at 19:21:17</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Técnicas para hablar fluido y claro - Teresa Baró • Comunicación de éxito</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Cuando hablas, ¿la gente se queda con la boca abierta o se aburre? Si es lo segundo, prepárate para tomar nota de las mejores técnicas y aprende cómo hablar de forma fluida, sin esfuerzo y sin aburrir a los demás. 

Fórmate con mis cursos 👉 https://bit.ly/TBcursos

🔽 También te puede interesar 🔽
Cómo usar la voz para influir y persuadir https://youtu.be/C2Hr99q2JBI
Los 3 pilares para hablar en público y disfrutar https://youtu.be/Lt05kaqHa08
De qué hablar cuando no sabemos de qué hablar https://youtu.be/W2ATY235XIQ
No cometas estos errores en una conversación https://youtu.be/twX49imskpI

👀 Mi libro &quot;La Gran Guía del lenguaje no verbal&quot; 👉 https://amzn.to/3fyxF2e

✔ Si eres mujer y quieres dar un gran salto en tu carrera, únete a la FÓRMULA IMPARABLE 👉 
https://www.teresabaro.com/es/formula_imparable/

📕  Mis libros https://www.teresabaro.com/mis-libros/

▶ Me puedes encontrar por mis redes sociales:
Twitter: https://twitter.com/tbarocatafau
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/tbarocatafau/
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/teresabarocom/ 
Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/teresa-baro-comunicacion-no-verbal/

▶ Conoce más sobre mi en: https://www.teresabaro.com/
▶ Descubre mis cursos: https://www.teresabaro.com/es/formate/]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.U2lWFRFwZLE</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/U2lWFRFwZLE.m4a" length="8771288" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 18:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/U2lWFRFwZLE/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>9</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Teresa Baró • Comunicación de éxito published on Thursday, July  7 2022 at 18:00:08</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Way To Launch Your Startup | Startup School - Y Combinator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Kat Mañalac is the head of YC&#x27;s Outreach team and advises early stage founders on their launches during the YC batch. She shares the multitude of ways to launch a product and how to get attention for them. Her talk provides tangible strategies and examples of startup launches and will change the way you think about launching.

Apply to Y Combinator: https://www.ycombinator.com/apply/
Work at a startup: https://www.ycombinator.com/jobs

Chapters (Powered by https://bit.ly/chapterme-yc) - 
00:00 - Launching Your Startup
01:28 - When Should I Launch My Startup?
03:42 - One Sentence Pitch
05:19 - How to Create a Short Memorable Description
09:17 - When is the X for Y Construction Not Too Cliche?
12:05 - Types of Launches
20:43 - Summary]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.u36A-YTxiOw</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/u36A-YTxiOw.m4a" length="20513048" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 17:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/u36A-YTxiOw/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>10</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Y Combinator published on Thursday, February  9 2023 at 22:44:27</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build An MVP | Startup School - Y Combinator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Y Combinator Group Partner, Michael Seibel, explains how to build a minimum viable product (MVP) for your startup idea. Using examples from real YC companies, Michael walks through how to determine your MVP feature set, build prototypes and demos for user testing, and present your MVP to early customers or investors.

Apply to Y Combinator: https://www.ycombinator.com/apply/ 
Work at a startup: https://www.ycombinator.com/jobs

Chapters (Powered by https://bit.ly/chapterme-yc) - 
00:00 - How to Build an Minimum Viable Product (MVP)?
01:50 - Pre-launch Startup Goals
04:26 - Founders Biggest Fear
07:17 - Examples - Software MVP
07:48 - Airbnb
08:36 - Twitch
09:15 - Stripe
10:36 - Solving Hair On Fire Problem
14:12 - Build an MVP Quickly
15:51 - Outro]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.QRZ_l7cVzzU</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/QRZ_l7cVzzU.m4a" length="16389640" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 17:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/QRZ_l7cVzzU/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>11</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Y Combinator published on Wednesday, March 15 2023 at 19:01:04</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-4, El Futuro de JavaScript, Sueldos en Tech | Raw Radio #3 ft Miguel Ángel Durán (Midudev) - hdeleon.net</title>
      <description><![CDATA[En este episodio hablaremos con Miguel Ángel Durán (Midudev), quien nos contará de que va la creación de contenido en Twitch, sobre los sueldos en programación, el burnout, el estrés, como ha sido el camino de JavaScript y que nos puede esperar con este lenguaje de Programación, y mucho más.

Redes de Miguel Ángel Durán (Midudev)
🟣Canal de Twitch: https://www.twitch.tv/midudev
🔴Canal Youtube: @midudev   
🌎Conferencia MiduFest: https://www.midufest.com/#ticket
🌎Sitio Web: https://midu.dev/
🐦Twitter: https://twitter.com/midudev

Mis Cursos de PROGRAMACIÓN: https://hdeleon.net/cursos-premium/

🖥️ Mi Monitor: https://amzn.to/3dtnDkk
⌨️ Mi Teclado: https://amzn.to/3BtjKnq
⌨️ Mi Deck elgato: https://amzn.to/3dvEKC3
🎧 Mis Orejeras: https://amzn.to/3BwQYm0
🎤 Mi Micrófono: https://amzn.to/3qPvFHh

Si quieres apoyarme y darme para una cerveza puedes hacerlo por aquí: http://paypal.me/HectorDeLeonGuevara

Puedes apoyarme desde 0.5 USD al mes uniéndote como miembro al canal aquí: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCDUdeFslCNoM29MAlZOfdWQ/join

Sígueme en Twitter ⇒  https://twitter.com/powerhdeleon
Mi Sitio web ⇒ http://hdeleon.net
Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/show/3obLU60alE7CGpzNeTS0kN

#programación #dev #javascript]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.FyfWESyvA2w</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/FyfWESyvA2w.m4a" length="63286259" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 22:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/FyfWESyvA2w/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>12</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by hdeleon.net published on Wednesday, March 15 2023 at 19:21:53</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden: "Doctors allow you to live; nurses make you want to live" - CBS News</title>
      <description><![CDATA[During a speech about mental health awareness, Vice President Joe Biden joked, &quot;doctors allow you to live; nurses make you want to live&quot; - before quickly clarifying: &quot;male nurses and female nurses.&quot;]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.PcTX04kW3Kw</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/PcTX04kW3Kw.m4a" length="1836092" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 22:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/PcTX04kW3Kw/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>13</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by CBS News published on Monday, June  3 2013 at 19:30:58</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuroscientist: This Simple Skill Will Make You More Powerful In Life | Andrew Huberman - Diy Things</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Neuroscientist: This Simple Skill Will Make You More Powerful In Life | Andrew Huberman

Also, in this video Neuroscientist - Andrew Huberman explains the 5 things in life which cannot be replaced.

Neuroscientist: There&#x27;s NO replacement for these 5 Things | Andrew Huberman. 2023

Neuroscientist Dr. Andrew Huberman shares his insights on the five habits that have no replacement when it comes to maintaining good health and well-being. He emphasizes the importance of getting enough sleep, regular exercise, a balanced and nutritious diet, socializing with others, and staying hydrated. 

 #andrewhuberman #huberman  #speech  #advice #motivation]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.g55rPgT4bj4</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/g55rPgT4bj4.m4a" length="6837098" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/g55rPgT4bj4/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>14</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Diy Things published on Monday, February  6 2023 at 20:25:23</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Aikman Talks Tom Brady's Retirement, Super Bowl Memories &amp; Cowboys 2023 Plan - Green Light with Chris Long</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Troy Aikman joins Chris Long to discuss Tom Brady&#x27;s retirement and how he&#x27;ll transition into broadcasting with FOX. Getting a call from Andy Reid to come out of retirement, favorite Super Bowl memories, and throwing the ball against Deion Sanders.

(00:00) - Troy talks Tom Brady&#x27;s retirement and his transition to the booth, calling games with Joe Buck and the New England vs Atlanta Super Bowl.
(13:55) - Troy&#x27;s Story of being called by Andy Reid to come out of retirement to play for the Eagles
(16:15) - Troy&#x27;s Super Bowl memories, victory parties and SBLVII predictions.
(29:00) - Cowboy&#x27;s areas of improvements and throwing the ball to Deion Sanders in the Super Bowl.

Listen to the Full Episode on Apple Podcasts and Spotify:

https://open.spotify.com/show/06jeyfm3I7IYGldmbp9AWu?si=0b10595a0266464b

https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/green-light-with-chris-long/id1485277290

Green Light Tube features the best content from the Green Light Podcast with Chris Long along with bonus video content from Chris, Macon, Nate, Cowboy Reid and a variety of exciting guests.  Follow our socials @greenlight on Twitter.  Follow Chris on Twitter @JOEL9ONE, Macon @Maconplays, Nate @BIGN98, and Cowboy Reid @reideranonymous.  Check in weekly for new videos. 
🌍🏀🏈SUBSCRIBE NOW ⚾🏒⛰️

#GreenLight #BlueWireVideo

www.greenlightpodcast.com]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.eP4raYsxyLo</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/eP4raYsxyLo.m4a" length="31079247" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 08:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/eP4raYsxyLo/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>15</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Green Light with Chris Long published on Friday, February  3 2023 at 00:52:02</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Coding Habits to Adopt in 2023 - Juan Carlos Fontecha</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Welcome to the new year! As software engineers, it&#x27;s important to continually improve and refine our skills to ensure we are writing high-quality, maintainable code. In this video, we&#x27;ll discuss some good coding habits that you can adopt in the new year to help you become a more efficient and effective programmer. Whether you&#x27;re a seasoned developer or just starting out, I&#x27;m hoping these habits will help you write better code and advance your career!

A couple of you were asking about the keyboard &amp; journal in the thumbnail, so here they are!
⌨️ Logitech MX Mechanical Mini: https://jfon.tech/thumbnail-keyboard
📕 Moleskin Classic (Plain): https://jfon.tech/dev-journal

If you&#x27;re interested in the equipment I use to record, I made a kit for it!
https://jfon.tech/yt-kit

📖 Chapters:
00:00 Intro
00:26 Breaking down your tasks
01:56 Impact of tiny improvements
03:21 Keeping a Dev Journal 
05:13 (Type)safety first
06:31 Eating the frog first
07:38 Meditate

🚀 Let&#x27;s connect
https://www.jcfontecha.com
https://www.twitter.com/jufontech
https://www.instagram.com/jfontech

#softwareengineer #bigtech #selfdevelopment #newyear #habits #2023 #newyearresolutions #coding #programming]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.QcnMvHpatW4</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/QcnMvHpatW4.m4a" length="8461026" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 18:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/QcnMvHpatW4/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>16</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Juan Carlos Fontecha published on Tuesday, December 20 2022 at 06:52:04</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Herd | Tom Brady has strong take on "stupid" Bill Belichick debate | Colin Cowherd reacts - UNDISPUTED SHOW</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Herd | Tom Brady has strong take on &quot;stupid&quot; Bill Belichick debate | Colin Cowherd reacts]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.TOo7iel3DzA</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/TOo7iel3DzA.m4a" length="11465617" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 19:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/TOo7iel3DzA/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>17</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by UNDISPUTED SHOW published on Tuesday, February  7 2023 at 17:18:34</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Herd | Colin Cowherd's reaction to Tom Brady's emotional retirement announcement - UNDISPUTED SHOW</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Herd | Colin Cowherd&#x27;s reaction to Tom Brady&#x27;s emotional retirement announcement]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.1dxA-wrQ7G8</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/1dxA-wrQ7G8.m4a" length="10791478" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 08:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/1dxA-wrQ7G8/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>18</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by UNDISPUTED SHOW published on Wednesday, February  1 2023 at 17:21:05</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Steve Jobs Heres To The Crazy Ones - Nathan Hulls</title>
      <description><![CDATA[http://www.NathanHulls.com

Steve Jobs narrates the first of Apples &#x27;Think Different&#x27; commercial &quot;Here&#x27;s to the Crazy Ones&quot;. It never aired. Richard Dreyfuss did the voice over for the original spot that aired.

&quot;The ones who are crazy enough to think that they can change the world, are the ones who do&quot;

http://www.nathanhulls.com]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.-z4NS2zdrZc</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/-z4NS2zdrZc.m4a" length="989115" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 23:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/-z4NS2zdrZc/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>19</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Nathan Hulls published on Wednesday, September 26 2012 at 03:42:01</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In The Night Garden Theme | Intro | Music | Titles - Cbeebies - High Quality - waybuloouk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[This is the intro to the popular pre school tv series In The Night Garden. Iggle Piggle, Upsy Daisy, Makka Pakka. 

Check out this Amazon In The Night Garden shop, delivery on orders over £5 are free: http://astore.amazon.co.uk/night-garden-toys-21

Or these other Amazon shops:
http://astore.amazon.co.uk/timmy-time-21
http://astore.amazon.co.uk/waybuloo-shop-21
http://astore.amazon.co.uk/pig-peppa-21
http://astore.amazon.co.uk/leapster-21]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.NQ5ku4z1pjs</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/NQ5ku4z1pjs.m4a" length="1980711" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 23:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/NQ5ku4z1pjs/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>20</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by waybuloouk published on Saturday, September 26 2009 at 17:55:07</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 ONE-MINUTE Habits That Save Me 20+ Hours a Week - Time Management For Busy People - Liam Porritt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The first 100 people to download Endel will get a free week of audio experiences - https://app.adjust.com/b8wxub6?campaign=liamporritt_January2023&amp;adgroup=youtube

In our busy lives, a few hours a week means time for a date, or a few hours of self-love pruning in the bath - so imagine what you could do with 10, 20 or even more extra time each week 🤯 

Well, from reading some of the best time management books out there, these are my top 4 quick habits to efficiently manage your time, which save me hours each week 🙌 They are simple, but hugely effective techniques to make the most of our 16 or so waking hours a day, and honestly are some of the core techniques that allow me to keep up a demanding career as a corporate lawyer, while running multiple businesses on the side 👨‍💻

The key to these habits is (as with all habits) consistency… kinda obvious, I know. But with these habits especially, they really don’t take much effort, but they do require a consistent consciousness of how you are working. So, try to keep each of these in mind as you get ready for, and then during, each of your work sessions 🫶

00:00 How I Juggle Everything
00:28 Cinema Mode
02:12 Batch By Project &amp; Task
06:27 Avoid Work
07:42 Multitask

………………………………………………….

Menos - Minimalist, sustainable design (by Liam &amp; Beth)

Sign up to get pre-launch access to one of only 200 grey and 400 black Menos backpack, made from recycled plastic - https://wearemenos.com ✨ 

Beth and I have created Menos to bring minimalist, sustainable design to help us all boss the everyday. Follow Menos (@wearemenos on Instagram) - https://instagram.com/wearemenos 

………………………………………………….

Get The Done App &amp; Other Productivity Apps - Completely Free For A Whole Year!

https://growthbundle.com/referral/?referrer=Liam&amp;referral-code=liamporritt&amp;source=partner

………………………………………………….

My Free Trello Masterclass

&#x27;More Focus, Less Stress - Build Your Ultimate Productivity System in Trello&#x27; is my FREE course (Trello is also FREE), which you can take by signing up for a free 2-week SkillShare trial: https://skl.sh/3h2XpV1

... The course walks you through how to build your customised version of my insanely powerful (but simple) Trello productivity system (aka the app that keeps me focused for 10 hours per day!) 📱

………………………………………………….

About Me

I&#x27;m a lawyer, part-time YouTuber, son, brother, startup founder, fiancé, black coffee drinker and plant dad. I graduated from Cambridge University (where I studied French and Spanish), topped my law school class and now work for a corporate law firm in London as a trainee solicitor (which takes up a lot of my time)!

Around that, I&#x27;m a big fan of discovering new ways of thinking, of balancing work with life, and of performing to the very best of my ability. Ohh, and being happy. And I try to share all that on this YouTube channel 😀

Fun fact: I believe we massively overplay the role of “natural talent” 😮 AND… I also believe that TOGETHER, WE ARE ALL CAPABLE OF POSITIVITY, PRODUCTIVITY AND SUCCESS.

📸  Instagram – https://www.instagram.com/liam.porritt/
🌍  My little kingdom – https://liamporritt.com

………………………………………………….

Thanks so much to Endel for sponsoring this video 😀]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.R5i8alK5hPo</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/R5i8alK5hPo.m4a" length="8899080" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 23:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/R5i8alK5hPo/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>21</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Liam Porritt published on Tuesday, January 24 2023 at 16:00:21</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
