<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Oliver's Personal Podcast</title>
    <link>http://oops.hopto.org:9090/oliver/publicprofile</link>
    <description>I publish interesting things !!!</description>
    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator> </generator>
    <language>es-ES</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:55:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <itunes:author>oliver</itunes:author>
    <managingEditor>oliver.barreto.online@gmail.com (oliver)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <itunes:category text="News"/>
    <itunes:image href="https://github.com/oliverbarreto/PersonalPodcast/raw/main/site-logo-1400x1400.png"/>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>oliver</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>oliver.barreto.online@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/oliverbarreto/PersonalPodcast/main/oliver_feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>The Groundbreaking Cancer Expert (New Research) This Common Food Is Making Cancer Worse! - The Diary Of A CEO</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Dr Thomas Seyfried is a Professor of biology, genetics, and biochemistry at Boston College. He has over 150 peer-reviewed publications and is also the author of books such as, ‘Cancer as a Metabolic Disease: On the Origin, Management, and Prevention of Cancer’. 

00:00 Intro  
01:59 What Would Dr Seyfried Say He Does?  
02:37 How Much Of A Problem Is Cancer Globally?  
04:30 What Types Of Cancer Are People Dying From?  
05:02 How Many People Will Develop Cancer?  
06:56 Where Does Cancer Rank In The Probabilities Of Taking My Life?  
08:12 What Is The Fermentation Process?  
12:16 How Have You Arrived At This Conclusion?  
16:52 Why Do Cancers Grow So Rapidly?  
19:17 What Are Ketones?  
21:23 What Can We Learn About Cancer From Our Ancestors?  
24:36 What Role Does Exercise Play In Fighting These Diseases?  
00:25:44 What Lifestyle Choices Are Causing The Cancer To Develop?  
29:07 Is Cancer Genetic?  
31:09 How Do We Keep Our Mitochondria Healthy?  
32:42 Is Cancer Genetic?  
36:27 Why Haven&#x27;t Opinions Changed Based On Dr Seyfried&#x27;s Evidence?  
38:27 If We Adopt This Mindset, What Will Happen To Cancer Statistics?  
39:17 Are The Current Cures Working?  
00:41:50 The Current Technologies Used To Prevent Cancer  
49:10 How Do We Prevent Cancer?  
51:06 Should I Be On A Keto Diet?  
54:57 Dr Seyfried&#x27;s Dog Study  
57:14 Human Cases Of People That Have Followed Your Research  
01:03:39 What Is Metabolic Therapy?  
01:04:36 What Should Someone That Has Cancer And Is Listening To This Do?  
01:07:52 Keto Plus Hyperbaric Oxygen Study  
01:11:57 Can You Have A Pre-Disposition To Cancer?  
01:12:28 Should I Restrict What I Eat, To Stave Off Cancer?  
01:13:16 What&#x27;s Your View On Fasting?  
01:13:58 How Do I Get Into The Keto State?  
01:17:10 Do We Need More Discipline?  
01:18:36 What Happens When You Fast?  
01:20:52 What Advice Would Dr Seyfried Give To His Kids?  
01:22:14 Why Isn&#x27;t Dr Seyfried Trying To Be Metabolically Perfect?  
01:23:04 What Food Laws Would Dr Seyfried Introduce?  
01:25:18 Is Dr Seyfried Hopeful?  
01:28:14 And What If You Are Successful?  
01:29:10 Are There Any Studies That Have Broken Dr Seyfried&#x27;s Heart?  
01:30:50 What Would Dr Seyfried Say To Someone Listening?  
01:32:55 Guest&#x27;s Last Question  You can purchase Dr Thomas’ book, ‘Keto for Cancer: Ketogenic Metabolic Therapy as a Targeted Nutritional Strategy’, here: https://g2ul0.app.link/1FotHad2pNb Follow Dr Thomas: 
Instagram - https://g2ul0.app.link/cwAePGF1pNb 
Twitter - https://g2ul0.app.link/0yuLM6I1pNb 

🌟 Get access to exclusive Diary of a CEO content: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCGq-a57w-aPwyi3pW7XLiHw/join

Get your hands on the brand new Diary Of A CEO Conversation Cards here: https://appurl.io/iUUJeYn25v

Follow me:
https://g2ul0.app.link/gnGqL4IsKKb 

Sponsors:
Shopify - http://shopify.com/bartlett]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.VaVC3PAWqLk</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/VaVC3PAWqLk.m4a" length="94729420" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 21:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/VaVC3PAWqLk/sddefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>0</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by The Diary Of A CEO published on Monday, October  7 2024 at 00:00:18</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“AI is bigger than the internet”How AI will change EVERYTHING Elon Musk Censorship  Marc Andreessen - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Big Shout-out to our Sponsors: Alty: If you’re looking for a partner in digital innovation, check out Alty for smarter and faster growth at https://bit.ly/3YdiCj7
Opus Clip: Get your first month of Opus Pro FREE at https://impacttheory.co/OpusClipITOct.
Netsuite: Spend less time looking backwards, and more time on what&#x27;s next. Download the CFO&#x27;s Guide to AI and Machine Learning at https://impacttheory.co/NetsuiteITOct.

Welcome to another thought-provoking episode of Impact Theory with Tom Bilyeu. Today, we&#x27;re diving into an in-depth conversation with the legendary entrepreneur and investor Mark Andreessen. Together, Tom and Mark navigate a wide range of topics, from the future of technology and AI to the dynamic complexities of the American economy and society.

Mark shares his optimism about America&#x27;s potential, driven by its diverse and ambitious population, while Tom raises pertinent questions about the looming challenges of inflation, government regulations, and economic growth. They explore how technological advancements, especially in AI and robotics, could revolutionize industries but also potentially clash with traditional values and societal norms.

We&#x27;ll delve into critical issues such as job displacement, censorship, and the evolving role of free speech in a rapidly changing world. Mark discusses the &quot;slow sectors&quot; of healthcare, education, and housing, emphasizing the pressing need for technological integration to reduce costs and drive growth.

This episode is packed with insights on the historical and future impacts of technology on the economy, the role of governmental regulations, and the ever-changing religious and cultural ideologies. Prepare to challenge your perspectives and gain a deeper understanding of the forces shaping our future. Buckle up; it’s a fascinating discussion you won&#x27;t want to miss!

00:00 🚀 How Companies Are Using AI and Robotics to Shape the Future!
17:57 🤖 From Sci-Fi to Reality: AI’s Explosive Growth!
25:24 💸 The Inflation Crisis: Why Your Savings Are Shrinking!
36:17 🏥 How Healthcare, Education, and Housing Are Fueling Inflation!
42:04 🔒 Are Licensing Requirements Just a Monopoly Scam?
58:22 🚨 AI Censorship Is Here—What You Need to Know!
01:05:55 🎭 The Hidden Power Struggles That Shape Our Culture!
01:22:20 📉 How IBM’s Corporate Hierarchy Killed Innovation!
01:31:41 🧠 The Social Impact of AI: What It Means for Human Interaction!
01:38:04 ❤️ Why Human Connections Matter More Than Ever—Even Fewer People Are Having Kids!
01:46:35 🕊 Why Religion No Longer Defines Culture and Genetics!
01:55:31 ⛪ Religion’s Secret Role in Building Strong Social Bonds!
02:06:05 📈 The Surprising Link Between Productivity and Innovation!

AI development, technological advancements, economic impact, United States economy, American people, government restraint, AI children, relationships with robots, cultural tensions, legal restrictions, regulatory burdens, Gulliver&#x27;s Travels analogy, rise in regulations, Elon Musk, government efficiency, Argentina&#x27;s economy, Javier Millet, deregulation, inflation control, existential questions, role of religion, job losses, secular ideologies, historical perspective on religion, modern religious flexibility, freedom of speech, censorship, job displacement, productivity growth, low fertility rates, societal meaning crisis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.6twxFu3bL0w</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/6twxFu3bL0w.m4a" length="126116676" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 22:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/6twxFu3bL0w/sddefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>1</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Tuesday, October 22 2024 at 06:53:40</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yuval Noah Harari They Are Lying About AI! The Trump Kamala Election Will Tear The Country Apart! - The Diary Of A CEO</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Yuval Noah Harari is a best-selling author, public intellectual and Professor of History at the Hebrew University of Jerusalem. He is the author of multi-million bestseller books such as, ‘Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind’ and ‘Homo Deus: A Brief History of Tomorrow’. 

00:00 Intro
02:31 Will Humans Continue To Rule The World?
06:48 Why AI Is The Biggest Game-Changer In History
10:34 Is AI Just Information Or Something More?
16:53 Can AI Manipulate Our Bank Accounts And Political Views?
21:42 How AI Will Affect Human Intimacy
23:44 Will AI Replace Teachers?
25:09 Why Online Information Is Junk
28:42 How Politicians Use Fear To Manipulate Us
31:52 Should There Be A Free Speech Movement
39:38 How Algorithms Are Shaping Global Politics And Increasing Fear
45:30 The Impact Of The US Election On Global Politics
48:48 What Trump Could Do To US Democracy
50:29 Can We Trust What We See On Social Media And The News?
55:37 Will AI Eventually Run Governments?
00:58:32 What Jobs Will AI Leave For Humans?
01:02:01 Which Jobs Will Be Automated By AI?
01:05:33 Is AI Conscious?
01:07:19 AI, Robots, And The Future Of Consciousness
01:10:01 Are We Living In A Simulation?
01:13:09 How Algorithms Control Our Lives
01:16:21 Understanding The AI Alignment Problem
01:21:13 The Relationship Between AI And Corporate Interests
01:25:04 The Growing Threat Of Totalitarian Governments
01:33:08 How The Algorithm Knows It&#x27;s Fake News
01:38:01 Is Yuval Tempted To Log Off?
01:41:52 Will Humans Become Two Species?
01:44:00 What&#x27;s The Solution To The Negatives Of AI?
01:49:17 The Guest&#x27;s Last Question

Follow Yuval: 
Instagram - https://g2ul0.app.link/7iXk5TnLAMb 
Twitter - https://g2ul0.app.link/eaKRt5rLAMb 

You can pre-order Yuval’s book ‘NEXUS: A Brief History of Information Networks from the Stone Age to AI’, here: https://amzn.to/4g8Vdrn 

My new book! &#x27;The 33 Laws Of Business &amp; Life&#x27; is out now - https://g2ul0.app.link/DOACBook 

Get your hands on the brand new Diary Of A CEO Conversation Cards here: https://appurl.io/iUUJeYn25v

Get access to exclusive Diary of a CEO members content here: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCGq-a57w-aPwyi3pW7XLiHw/join

Follow me:
https://g2ul0.app.link/gnGqL4IsKKb 

Sponsors:
Linkedin Jobs: linkedin/doac]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.78YN1e8UXdM</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/78YN1e8UXdM.m4a" length="110959272" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 18:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/78YN1e8UXdM/sddefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>2</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by The Diary Of A CEO published on Thursday, September  5 2024 at 00:00:03</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors' Principles of Silicon Valley Taught in Stanford MBA  Ilya Strebulaev - EO</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Today, we&#x27;ve invited Professor Ilya Strebulaev, who has taught and researched venture capital at Stanford MBA for 20 years. While studying Silicon Valley investors, he focused on those consistently making successful investments. He defined this concept as the &#x27;venture mindset.&#x27; What decision models do Silicon Valley investors use, and how can we apply them to our lives? Let&#x27;s find out in the video!

To purchase 『The Venture Mindset』: https://a.co/d/05vv5Jaq

00:00 Intro
00:49 Chapter 1. Who Are the Venture Capitalists
03:34 Chapter 2. The Venture Mindset
11:34 Chapter 3. Tips to Write a Must-Read Blurb
15:17 Chapter 4. Strikeouts Are Strikeouts

EO stands for Entrepreneurship &amp; Opportunities. As we&#x27;re looking to feature more inspiring stories of entrepreneurs all over the world, don&#x27;t hesitate to contact us at partner@eoeoeo.net

EO Builders Club | A Membership Community for certified founders &amp; global entrepreneurs, connected through EO&#x27;s powerful resources
Enter Now 👉 https://bit.ly/3TQfmYW

Twitter | @EO__Global 
LinkedIn | @EO STUDIO 
Instagram | @eostudio.gl 

EO Podcast 🎧
- Spotify: https://bit.ly/442cRa1
- Apple Podcast: https://apple.co/3oH3NHC
- Google Podcast: https://bit.ly/40E1d2v

Subtitles for this video were created using [XL8.ai](http://xl8.ai/) machine translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.Q3EE-V-cMog</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/Q3EE-V-cMog.m4a" length="16090588" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 13:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Q3EE-V-cMog/sddefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>3</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by EO published on Tuesday, July  2 2024 at 07:00:30</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Ollama and N8N for AI Automation - Matt Williams</title>
      <description><![CDATA[In this video, Matt Williams, a founding member of the Ollama team, dives deep into the world of AI automation using n8n. Discover how this powerful workflow automation tool can revolutionize your productivity and streamline your processes.

🔑 Key Points:
• Introduction to n8n and its capabilities
• Comparison with other automation tools
• Setting up n8n (cloud-hosted vs. self-hosted)
• Real-world examples of AI-powered workflows
• Integrating Ollama and other AI models
• Tips for creating efficient automations

🛠️ Learn how to:
• Automate news aggregation and social media posting
• Generate AI summaries of web content
• Backup your workflows effortlessly
• Integrate with popular services like Supabase, GitHub, and more

Whether you&#x27;re an AI enthusiast, a productivity junkie, or just curious about automation, this video is packed with insights to help you master AI automation fast!

👍 Like, Subscribe, and hit the notification bell to stay updated on the latest AI and automation tips!

#AIAutomation #n8n #Productivity #Ollama #WorkflowAutomation

Be sure to sign up to my monthly newsletter at https://technovangelist.substack.com/subscribe

You can find the Technovangelist discord at: https://discord.gg/uS4gJMCRH2
The Ollama discord is at https://discord.gg/ollama

(they have a pretty url because they are paying at least $100 per month for Discord. You help get more viewers to this channel and I can afford that too.)

Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHaF9kM2wn8C3CLRwLkC2GQ/join

Or if you prefer there is also a Patreon: https://patreon.com/technovangelist


00:00 - Intro
01:02 - The Platform
01:28 - Recent Updates
01:42 - But what is it?
02:10 - The Predecessors and Alternatives
03:01 - At least 3 Ways to run it
04:27 - Why two?
05:26 - Look at my cloud instance
06:02 - Templates
06:17 - Look at a workflow
07:37 - Community Nodes
08:36 - Exporting a flow
09:20 - Triggering the workflow
09:49 - Sending the tweet
10:53 - The AI flow
11:51 - Not perfect]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.VDuA5xbkEjo</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/VDuA5xbkEjo.m4a" length="13314279" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 12:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/VDuA5xbkEjo/sddefault.jpg?v=67009598"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>4</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Matt Williams published on Friday, October  4 2024 at 18:30:24</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We're On The Brink Of Collapse - How The Everything Bubble Will Crash The Economy  Peter Schiff - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Special Thanks to our Sponsors: ZBiotics: Head to https://zbiotics.com/impact  and use the code IMPACT at checkout for 15% off.
Found Banking: Sign up for Found for FREE today at https://www.found.com/impact 

Welcome to another eye-opening episode of Impact Theory with Tom Bilyeu. Today, we delve into the looming economic turbulence with financial expert Peter Schiff. In this episode, titled &quot;We&#x27;re On The Brink Of Collapse - How The Everything Bubble Will Crash The Economy,&quot; we explore the potential downfall of the U.S. dollar as the reserve currency and its ripple effects on inflation and consumer goods.

Peter Schiff pulls no punches as he shares his insights on the monumental challenge of rebuilding U.S. manufacturing amidst high government regulations and taxes. He reveals the stark contrast between government-reported economic health and the reality of high inflation, unemployment, and a contracting economy. We discuss the power of media and political manipulation of public perception and the true cost of inflation, equating price increases to a hidden tax burdening citizens.

Schiff discusses strategic steps to protect your wealth, including investing in high-dividend, inflation-resistant companies globally, and stockpiling non-perishable goods. Additionally, he highlights the dangerous potential for a sudden, severe inflation spike and the importance of diversifying investments into precious metals and foreign markets.

We also cover the broader impacts of the U.S.&#x27;s economic policies on global trade and the precarious position of the dollar. Schiff argues for a return to the gold standard, scrutinizes contemporary political promises, and the implications of price controls, predicting a future where inflation accelerates and living costs soar.

Join us as we navigate these complex financial landscapes and uncover strategies to safeguard your financial future in uncertain times. Whether you&#x27;re an investor, a concerned citizen, or someone passionate about economic policy, this episode is packed with crucial insights and practical advice. Stay tuned!

00:00 Government manipulates CPI, affecting inflation perception.
14:21 High interest rates would bankrupt the government.
28:56 Creating inflation harms everyone, unfairly distributing losses.
35:30 AI-driven productivity might reduce debt, improve living.
45:53 Federal Reserve pays profits back to the government.
55:12 Harris criticizes Biden while claiming bidenomics success.
01:09:28 ID laws vary; Puerto Ricans can&#x27;t vote federally.
01:19:21 Constitutional checks eroded; government ignoring prohibitions.
01:28:51 Tax on appreciated assets would destroy economy.
01:34:54 Government regulation raises prices; market uses competition.
01:44:26 Invest in high-dividend, inflation-resistant essential businesses.
02:03:41 Dollar decline will trigger inflation and exodus.
02:10:14 Identify valuable stocks in promising sectors.
02:23:53 Choose bullion for value, investments for returns.
02:26:15 Multiple jobs, no savings, massive credit card debt.


dollar reserve currency, U.S. manufacturing, economic manipulation, public perception, high inflation, unemployment rates, Kamala Harris leadership, media influence, investment strategy, foreign investments, global economic impact, portfolio construction, government spending, price controls, inflation protection, U.S. bonds, corporate bonds, dividend-paying companies, gold standard endorsement, Federal Reserve policies, democracy vs. republic, taxing unrealized gains, housing market policies, debt and interest rates, hyperinflation, fiat currencies, social media presence, gold price prediction, reserve currency status, remonetizing gold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.Z8ZrGle8Bss</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/Z8ZrGle8Bss.m4a" length="143951064" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Z8ZrGle8Bss/sddefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>5</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Tuesday, September 10 2024 at 06:00:43</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Google CEO's BANNED Interview LEAKED You Have No Idea What's Coming - AI Upload</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Ex-Google CEO Eric Schmidt recently made headlines with some controversial comments about AI during an interview conduced at Stanford University. This interview was taken down at his request after he admitted to misspeaking. But did Eric Schmidt actually let on to something big coming in terms of the future of AI?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.EUeryhp8HSQ</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/EUeryhp8HSQ.m4a" length="26696524" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 07:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/EUeryhp8HSQ/sddefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>6</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by AI Upload published on Monday, August 26 2024 at 11:19:57</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Ocean HD 1080p Video with Beach Sounds - 4 Hour Long! - LoungeV Films - Relaxing Music and Nature Sounds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The films with relaxing tropical ocean sounds shown in this video with nature sounds are available on the official site of LoungeV studio in the original full HD 1080p quality video. Look for &quot;Caribbean Lounge&quot; discounted package and &quot;Infinity Blue&quot; film with ocean waves and stunning scenery: ☯☯☯ http://www.LoungeV.com ☯☯☯

Copyright © 2011-2018
Contact us for licensing questions: http://www.loungev.com/contact/]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.4mEbABPtTv8</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/4mEbABPtTv8.m4a" length="264047064" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 19:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4mEbABPtTv8/sddefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>7</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by LoungeV Films - Relaxing Music and Nature Sounds published on Tuesday, January  7 2014 at 14:18:17</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Creator Reveals the Future Of Programming with AI - Matthew Berman</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Let&#x27;s look at what Linus Torvalds, the creator of Linux, thinks about the future of programming with AI. 

Join My Newsletter for Regular AI Updates 👇🏼
https://www.matthewberman.com

My Links 🔗
👉🏻 Main Channel: https://www.youtube.com/@matthew_berman
👉🏻 Clips Channel: https://www.youtube.com/@matthewbermanclips
👉🏻 Twitter: https://twitter.com/matthewberman
👉🏻 Discord: https://discord.gg/xxysSXBxFW
👉🏻 Patreon: https://patreon.com/MatthewBerman
👉🏻 Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/matthewberman_ai
👉🏻 Threads: https://www.threads.net/@matthewberman_ai
👉🏻 LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/company/forward-future-ai

Need AI Consulting? 📈
https://forwardfuture.ai/

Media/Sponsorship Inquiries ✅ 
https://bit.ly/44TC45V

Chapters:
00:15 - Famous computer scientist
01:48 - AI code assistance
02:58 - Next abstraction level
03:41 - Language model evolution
05:47 - Obvious bug detection
07:30 - Human pattern recognition
10:14 - Continuous human errors
11:55 - Caution against hype
12:34 - AI&#x27;s positive influences
14:05 - Natural language applications
15:27 - Improved development tools
18:14 - Importance of open data]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.fVXl00PrM3s</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/fVXl00PrM3s.m4a" length="19188197" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fVXl00PrM3s/sddefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>8</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Matthew Berman published on Wednesday, August 28 2024 at 08:41:04</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Agent Send Your Children To A Village! How To Detect A Lie Instantly! - Evy Poumpouras - The Diary Of A CEO</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Evy Poumpouras is a former U.S. Secret Service Special Agent and multi-media journalist. She is also the co-host of Bravo TV&#x27;s series ‘Spy Games’ and author of the best-selling memoir, ‘Becoming Bulletproof’.

00:00 Intro 
02:22 My Mission To Unlock People&#x27;s Potential
05:05 How You Became A Secret Service Officer
10:43 How To Get Someone To Do What You Want Them To
13:10 When You Listen To Someone They Like You More
14:34 You Need To Know About Them And Then You Can Start Asking The Right Questions
18:18 How To Get Others To Respect You
22:59 Is It Your Ego Or Have Your Boundaries Being Broken?
26:49 How To Build Confidence
29:34 The Different Versions Of Ourselves We Create
32:49 What I Learnt About Leadership From Working With 4 US Presidents
35:47 I Was In The Room When US Presidents Would Make Tough Decisions
38:36 My First Day Working For George Bush
41:07 Secret Service Training: Only 1% Make It Through
44:16 The 1% Of People That Became Part Of The Secret Service
46:06 How Can You Tell If Someone Is Lying To You?
48:16 Who&#x27;s The Biggest Liar You&#x27;ve Met?
50:54 Signs They&#x27;re Lying To You
52:59 What Your Body Language Reveals About You
01:00:19 Do Men Struggle With Strong Women?
01:01:00 What Advice Would You Give Your Daughter Become A Resilient Person
01:04:37 What Do You Work Out Your Mind And Body
01:07:19 What Was The Scariest Day Of Your Career?
01:12:28 How Was Your Mental Health During Your Career?
01:17:48 Discrimination In The Secret Service
01:19:39 How To Be Heard And Respected
01:25:51 Why You Need To Take Personal Responsibility
01:33:48 The Addiction To Being A Victim
01:35:02 Identifying Victims That Don&#x27;t Want To Change
01:39:47 Undercover Missions
01:45:24 Discrimination In The Job
01:50:58 Labelling Yourself Can Affect The Way You See Yourself

You can purchase Evy’s book, ‘Becoming Bulletproof’, here: https://amzn.to/3yOiwFN 

Follow Evy: 
Instagram - https://bit.ly/4aN4q4D 
Twitter - https://bit.ly/4c4TErD 

My new book! &#x27;The 33 Laws Of Business &amp; Life&#x27; is out now - https://smarturl.it/DOACbook

Follow me:
https://beacons.ai/diaryofaceo  

Sponsors:
PerfectTed: http://bit.ly/PerfectTed-DOAC with an exclusive code DIARY10 for 10% off
ZOE: http://joinzoe.com with an exclusive code CEO10 for 10% off]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.iz_SJ5TpLJ0</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/iz_SJ5TpLJ0.m4a" length="119903141" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iz_SJ5TpLJ0/sddefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>9</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by The Diary Of A CEO published on Thursday, June  6 2024 at 00:00:19</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Schmidt Full Controversial Interview on AI Revolution (Former Google CEO) - Financial Wise</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#elonmusk #samaltman #tiktok #google #ceo #tech #ai #technology #nvidia #intel #openai #microsoft #chatgpt #llm #gemini #robotics #software #programming #internet #promptengineering 

Welcome to Financial Wise!
I provide educational content on tech &amp; market and feature Elon Musk and other tech &amp; market celebrities. Make sure to subscribe! https://youtube.com/@OfficialFinancialWise

Recorded: Stanford]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.mKVFNg3DEng</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/mKVFNg3DEng.m4a" length="43102563" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/mKVFNg3DEng/sddefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>10</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Financial Wise published on Sunday, August 18 2024 at 06:43:50</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Asking Questions - Andrew Bustamante</title>
      <description><![CDATA[In this clip of The David Pakman Show, we discuss the art of asking questions.

Find your Spy Superpower: https://yt.everydayspy.com/4e5PIsm

If you like this, click subscribe, like and share with a friend.

andrew bustamante,everyday spy podcast,spy,lex fridman,andrew bustamante podcast,cia,manipulating minds,persuasion,red pill,fresh and fit,security clearance,everydayspy,everyday spy,intelligence missions,intelligence community,everydayspy podcast,trust building,building relationships,trust dynamics,social engineering,mastering trust,psychology,top cia psychology hacks,psychology hacks,asking questions,power of asking questions,sales]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.bTGfB1iQwW8</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/bTGfB1iQwW8.m4a" length="2255870" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 19:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/bTGfB1iQwW8/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>11</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Andrew Bustamante published on Saturday, June  8 2024 at 15:00:37</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-OpenAI Employee Just Revealed it ALL! - TheAIGRID</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Join My Private Community - https://www.patreon.com/TheAIGRID
🐤 Follow Me on Twitter https://twitter.com/TheAiGrid
🌐 Checkout My website - https://theaigrid.com/


Links From Todays Video:
https://situational-awareness.ai/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/situationalawareness.pdf

Welcome to my channel where i bring you the latest breakthroughs in AI. From deep learning to robotics, i cover it all. My videos offer valuable insights and perspectives that will expand your knowledge and understanding of this rapidly evolving field. Be sure to subscribe and stay updated on my latest videos.

Was there anything i missed?

(For Business Enquiries)  contact@theaigrid.com

#LLM #Largelanguagemodel #chatgpt
#AI
#ArtificialIntelligence
#MachineLearning
#DeepLearning
#NeuralNetworks
#Robotics
#DataScience]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.om5KAKSSpNg</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/om5KAKSSpNg.m4a" length="51201977" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 19:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/om5KAKSSpNg/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>12</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by TheAIGRID published on Saturday, June  8 2024 at 13:30:31</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los SECRETOS Más Oscuros de la Élite al fin REVELADOS | Mario Conde - Inversión Racional Podcast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[¡Bienvenidos a nuestro último episodio del podcast! En la entrevista de hoy, Luis Miguel Ortiz tiene el placer de entrevistar a Mario Conde. 

En este fascinante episodio, tenemos el placer de conversar con Mario Conde, una figura que ha sido central en diversos debates sobre política, economía y sociedad. Comenzamos explorando quién es Mario Conde y qué actividades lo ocupan actualmente, estableciendo el contexto para una discusión más profunda sobre temas críticos que afectan a nuestra sociedad.

Adentrándonos más en la discusión, evaluamos si las élites que nos gobiernan han cambiado con el tiempo y abordamos temas como la regulación de la circulación del dinero y sus implicaciones en la libertad personal y económica. Mario comparte su visión sobre cómo la sociedad podría cambiar El Sistema, promoviendo un debate sobre la igualdad ante la ley y cómo los individuos pueden protegerse dentro de un marco legal a menudo complicado.

Una conversación esencial para cualquiera interesado en entender las dinámicas de poder y cambio en la sociedad contemporánea. No te pierdas esta oportunidad de profundizar en temas que definirán el rumbo de nuestras vidas. ¡Asegúrate de suscribirte para no perderte futuros diálogos iluminadores!

🤝 Conoce a Scalable Capital: https://bit.ly/scalableinversionracional

🔗 Aprende a invertir como un profesional con nuestro curso avanzado: https://www.inversionracional.com/curso

📝 Notas de los episodio y bibliografía aquí: https://www.inversionracional.com/podcast/ 

CRONOLOGÍA: 
0:00 Inicio
2:19 Introducción
3:23 ¿Quién es Mario Conde?
5:03 ¿A qué se dedica Mario Conde?
6:54 ¿Por qué debes ver este podcast?
9:30 ¿Qué es la libertad?
18:20 ¿En qué consiste “El Sistema”?
22:15 ¿Cómo toma decisiones El Sistema?
29:26 ¿Los ciudadanos pueden vivir fuera del Sistema?
34:59 ¿Las élites que nos gobiernan son las mismas de antes?
42:59 ¿Se debe controlar la libre circulación del dinero?
56:26 Cómo la sociedad puede cambiar El Sistema
1:01:00 ¿Somos iguales ante la ley?
1:02:03 ¿Cómo te puedes proteger ante la ley?
1:12:28 ¿El dólar perderá su predominancia en el mundo?
1:38:44 ¿Qué pasa con los jóvenes que se van de España?
1:41:27 ¿Qué sucede con el sistema de pensiones?
1:45:44 Situación del sector agrícola en España
1:48:30 ¿Qué futuro nos espera con la IA?
1:58:30 PREGUNTAS RÁPIDAS
2:03:11 Despedida

📌 ¡No olvides suscribirte y dejar tus recomendaciones en comentarios!]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.g14P5_Kaosc</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/g14P5_Kaosc.m4a" length="120723840" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/g14P5_Kaosc/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>13</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Inversión Racional Podcast published on Tuesday, April 23 2024 at 14:24:23</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Bilyeu &amp; His Wife EXPOSE Red Pill, What Women Desire &amp; How To Become Irresistible | Lisa Bilyeu - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Thank you to today’s sponsors:
Hartford Gold: Get $15K in FREE silver: https://bit.ly/ITGold
Aura Frames: $30 Off + Free shipping: https://bit.ly/AuraFrameIT

Be sure to get your copy of Lisa’s book, Radical Confidence, here: https://radicalconfidence.com/

Traditional roles for men and women in both personal and professional contexts are rapidly changing, and if you want to play the dating game to win and find a mate, you need to understand what makes women tick and how to be authentic while also desirable and irresistible. 

In today’s episode of Impact Theory, I’m joined by my wife Lisa Bilyeu for a super deep, insightful conversation around what women actually desire in a guy and WHY; how to become irresistible to the opposite sex; and the complexities of personal choices in the context of societal expectations, gender roles, and personal fulfillment.

Lisa Bilyeu is an entrepreneur, producer, best-selling author, public speaker, and host inspiring and empowering women (and men!) to build their confidence and change their life. Lisa co-founded the billion-dollar brand Quest Nutrition, is co-founder and president of Impact Theory Studios, and she has built a global audience while creating an impressive slate of content that has been viewed over half a billion times.

Be sure to get your copy of Lisa’s recently updated book, Radical Confidence, here: https://radicalconfidence.com/

We are digging deep into: 
- the intricacies of deciding NOT to have children in your relationship
- effects of societal pressures on individual decisions
- dynamics of a healthy relationship
- the struggles and fulfillment that come with ANY decision
- impacts of birth control on relationship dynamics
- shifting perceptions of relationships in modern times
- platforms like OnlyFans and their role in changing the dynamics of sexuality and personal expression
- the concept of &quot;hypergamy&quot; and societal views on relationships
- need for self-awareness and courage to pursue your ideal life
- the importance of communication and mutual respect in relationships

Lisa and I also go head to head as we explore how platforms like OnlyFans can be both empowering and exploitative, the most effective the decision-making processes you can use when it comes to big decisions, and the importance of making your own choices without fear of external criticism. 

Be sure to get your copy of Lisa’s book, Radical Confidence, here: https://radicalconfidence.com/

Chapter Markers:

[0:00] Challenges in finding love
[18:06] Hypergamy and women&#x27;s choices
[43:53] Dynamics and expectations in relationships
[1:14:51] Consequences of promiscuity
[1:40:46] Human vs robot connection
[2:02:21] Balancing work, family, and potential regrets
[3:05:32] Beliefs aligned with evolution

Be sure to get your copy of Radical Confidence, just updated with a new chapter and released in paperback, here: https://radicalconfidence.com/


Follow Lisa Bilyeu: 
Website: https://www.radicalconfidence.com/ 
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/lisabilyeu/ 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/lisabilyeu 
Order “Radical Confidence”: www.radicalconfidence.com/ 

Follow Tom Bilyeu: 
Website: https://impacttheoryuniversity.com/ 
X: https://twitter.com/TomBilyeu
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tombilyeu/


If you want to dive deeper into my content, search through every episode, find specific topics I&#x27;ve covered, and ask me questions. Go to my Dexa page: https://dexa.ai/tombilyeu

Themes: Mindset, Finance, World Affairs, Health &amp; Productivity, Future &amp; Tech, Simulation Theory &amp; Physics, Dating &amp; Relationships


Follow Lisa Bilyeu: 
Website: https://www.radicalconfidence.com/ 
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/lisabilyeu/ 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/lisabilyeu 
Order “Radical Confidence”: www.radicalconfidence.com/ 

Follow Tom Bilyeu: 
Website: https://impacttheoryuniversity.com/ 
X: https://twitter.com/TomBilyeu
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tombilyeu/

If you want to dive deeper into my content, search through every episode, find specific topics I&#x27;ve covered, and ask me questions. Go to my Dexa page: https://dexa.ai/tombilyeu

Themes: Mindset, Finance, World Affairs, Health &amp; Productivity, Future &amp; Tech, Simulation Theory &amp; Physics, Dating &amp; Relationships]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.-VFz5yO2SO4</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/-VFz5yO2SO4.m4a" length="192148183" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 15:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/-VFz5yO2SO4/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>14</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Tuesday, April 30 2024 at 13:00:00</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>136. The Art of Disagreeing Without Conflict: Navigating the Nuance | Think Fast, Talk Smart:... - Stanford Graduate School of Business</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Disagreement and conflict may look the same on the surface, but the two concepts are, in fact, very different. According to Julia Minson, knowing how these notions differ is crucial to how you approach them. 

In this episode of Think Fast Talk Smart, Minson (https://www.linkedin.com/in/julia-minson-5b511b150/) and strategic communication lecturer Matt Abrahams delve into the intricacies of conflict and disagreement. Minson, an associate professor of public policy at the Harvard Kennedy School and Stanford University alumna, also shares her expertise on decision-making and conflict negotiation. Minson emphasizes the need for genuine curiosity and receptiveness in communication to foster productive dialogue.

Think Fast, Talk Smart (https://www.gsb.stanford.edu/business-podcasts/think-fast-talk-smart-podcast) is a podcast produced by Stanford Graduate School of Business. Each episode provides concrete, easy-to-implement tools and techniques to help you hone and enhance your communication skills.

Episode Reference Links:
Julia Minson: Website (http://www.juliaminson.com/) Underestimating Counterparts’ Learning Goals Impairs Conflictual Conversations (http://www.juliaminson.com/uploads/1/1/3/1/113175333/collins_dorison_gino___minson_2022.pdf) (Julia’s study about people’s goals when talking to those they disagree with) To have better disagreements, change your words (https://shorensteincenter.org/commentary/better-disagreements-change-words-4-ways-make-counterpart-feel-heard-keep-conversation-going/) (Article by Julia about HEAR) Ep.30 - Dissolve Disagreements: How Communication Impacts Conflict: Website (https://www.gsb.stanford.edu/insights/dissolve-disagreements-how-communication-impacts-conflict) / YouTube (https://youtu.be/8vTeknRSjW4?feature=shared) Ep.72 - Quick Thinks: Talk it Out - How to Successfully Negotiate and Resolve Conflict: Website (https://www.gsb.stanford.edu/insights/quick-thinks-talk-it-out-how-successfully-negotiate-resolve-conflict) / YouTube (https://youtu.be/hfl89lUzF3c?feature=shared) 
Connect:
Email Questions &amp; Feedback thinkfast@stanford.edu Episode Transcripts Think Fast Talk Smart Website (https://www.gsb.stanford.edu/business-podcasts/think-fast-talk-smart-podcast) Newsletter Signup + English Language Learning FasterSmarter.io (http://fastersmarter.io/) Think Fast Talk Smart LinkedIn Page (https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/77761391/) , Instagram (https://www.instagram.com/thinkfasttalksmart/) , YouTube (https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLxq_lXOUlvQDgCVFj9L79kqJybW0k6OaB) Matt Abrahams LinkedIn (https://www.linkedin.com/in/maabrahams/) Stanford GSB LinkedIn (https://www.linkedin.com/school/stanford-graduate-school-of-business/) &amp; Twitter (https://twitter.com/stanfordgsb) 



Chapters:

(00:00:00) Introduction

Matt introduces guest Julia Minson, who is an expert in decision-making, conflict negotiation, and the psychology of disagreement.

(00:00:54) Journey into Conflict and Disagreement Research

Julia gives insight into her background and what led her to research disagreement and conflict.

(00:01:55) Distinguishing Between Disagreement and Conflict

The difference between disagreement and conflict, and why understanding this distinction is crucial for effective communication.

(00:04:12) Strategies for Disagreeing Better

Practical advice on how to disagree constructively without escalating to conflict, focusing on expressing and acting with curiosity.

(00:07:05) Demonstrating Curiosity and Conversational Receptiveness

Tactics for showing curiosity and conversational receptiveness, including using the HEAR acronym to maintain constructive dialogues.

(00:14:38) Managing Conflict

Managing and navigating conflict, emphasizing emotional readiness and the importance of choosing battles wisely.

(00:18:25) The Final Three Questions

Julia shares personal experiences with conflict and disagreement, a communicator she admires, and her recipe for successful communication.

(00:22:48) Conclusion




See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy (https://art19.com/privacy) and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info (https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info).

Episode link: https://play.headliner.app/episode/20034776?utm_source=youtube]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.VQTsDsPNSTw</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/VQTsDsPNSTw.m4a" length="24679889" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/VQTsDsPNSTw/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>15</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Stanford Graduate School of Business published on Tuesday, April  2 2024 at 15:03:53</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Finish One Month of Work Today - Rian Doris</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A revolutionary method to 30x your productivity.
Get the One-Month Day Checklist: https://www.flowstate.com/onemonthday

ABOUT ME
Rían Doris is the Co-Founder &amp; CEO of Flow Research Collective, the world’s leading peak performance research and training institute focused on decoding the neuroscience of flow states and helping leaders and their teams unlock flow states consistently. Clients include Accenture, Audi, Facebook, Bain &amp; the US Airforce.

Along with being listed on Forbes 30 Under 30 Rian&#x27;s thought leadership has been featured in Fast Company, PBS and Big Think and he hosts Flow Research Collective Radio, an iTunes top 10 science podcast.

Rían is also the Executive Chairman &amp; Owner of Consulting.com. On the side, Rian does some angel investing in health and performance companies like Levels Health, Neurohacker Collective, The Way &amp; Myodetox.
‍
Rían holds a degree in Philosophy, Politics &amp; Economics (PPE) from Trinity College Dublin, an MSc in Neuroscience at King&#x27;s College, London and an MBA. Rian is currently pursuing a PhD at the University of Birmingham—focusing on how flow states affect perceived meaning in life.
‍
Prior to co-founding Flow Research Collective with Steven Kotler, Rian worked with NYT Bestselling Author Keith Ferazzi, and 12X NYT Bestselling Author Dr. Dan Siegel, distinguished fellow of the American Psychiatric Association.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.Q7Phkq0BUXM</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/Q7Phkq0BUXM.m4a" length="26500931" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 07:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/Q7Phkq0BUXM/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>16</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Rian Doris published on Thursday, March 21 2024 at 12:00:18</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>¿QUÉ HAY DETRÁS DE LA POSIBLE DIMISIÓN DE SÁNCHEZ? - Vlog de Marc Vidal - Marc Vidal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Intervención en &#x27;Horizonte&#x27; sobre que hay detrás de la posible dimisión de Sánchez y los indicios que el software espía Pegasus pueda estar detrás. Con la participación de Angel Niño, el Coronel Baños, Alejandro Entrambasaguas y obviamente, Iker Jiménez y Carmen Porter.

Puedes ver el programa completo en https://www.cuatro.com/horizonte/a-la-carta/20240426/programa-video-completo_18_012333968.html

💳 Donativo https://bit.ly/donativomarcvidal 
🔥 Bitcoin https://zbd.gg/mvidal 

📽️ Subscríbete → https://bit.ly/3H3UTKe
🔔 Activa las notificaciones 

Y sígueme también en:

🔊 Podcast → https://spoti.fi/3pQWk64
📽️ Youtube → https://bit.ly/3H3UTKe 
📘 Mis libros → https://amzn.to/3r11sFQ
📷 Instagram → https://lnkd.in/dNvTFaQ
🐦 Twitter → https://lnkd.in/d3ZU6Nw
🔗 Blog → https://www.marcvidal.net
🛡️ Telegram → https://t.me/marcvidal_telegram

🔴  Desmiento tener canales en redes sociales dedicados a recomendaciones de inversión o solicitudes de dinero. Cualquier perfil o comentario que afirme lo contrario, usando mi nombre o imagen, está buscando estafar. ¡No caigas en el engaño! 

#dimision #television #pedrosánchez]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.vPVCdSDH0EY</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/vPVCdSDH0EY.m4a" length="36146811" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/vPVCdSDH0EY/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>17</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Marc Vidal published on Saturday, April 27 2024 at 15:34:27</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Spy: "This Could Spark WW3 In 2024"- China's Takeover &amp; Iran-Israel-Palestine |Andrew Bustamante - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Thank you to today’s sponsors:
Ground News: Go to https://bit.ly/GroundImpact and you can get 40% off unlimited access this month
AG1: 

On today’s episode of Impact Theory, former CIA spy Andrew Bustamante and I are delving deep into the unsettling realities of our chaotic world. 

Andrew is sharing invaluable insights from his time as a CIA spy, offering a unique perspective on the distressing prospect of America turning against itself and the increasing potential for war. We also get Andrew’s ideas on how external attacks on our system could ironically unify us, but also how these threats are being weaponized to destabilize America. 

We also touch on: 
- How the new world power transition plays out over the next 10 years 
- The bloodless war in China to keep your eye on
- Foreign power influence in US elections
- U.S. domestic and foreign policy challenges
- The need for U.S. policy reassessment in the Middle East
- Historical solutions and their applicability to current conflicts
- The strategic, economic, and military partnership between the U.S. and Israel
- The plight of Palestinian people and potential solutions
- Analysis of historical superpower phases and predictions based on economic cycles
- Impact of espionage on global politics
- The role of cultural understanding and unity in addressing international threats and conflicts

It’s near impossible to not be impacted on various levels by the role of the internet in accelerating the velocity of information. 

It’s near impossible to not be impacted on various levels by the role of the internet in accelerating the velocity of information. We’re in a time where enabling psychological manipulation on a massive scale is happening right now as we speak. 

As we face an increasingly complex and confusing era, understanding the tactics and strategies used to manipulate you has never been more crucial.

Find your Spy Superpower with Andrew here: https://everydayspy.com/spyquiz   


Chapter Markers:

[0:00] Economic cycle predicts war
[29:04] Israel vs. Palestine conflict 
[1:10:53] Negotiation for off ramps amid Ukraine crisis
[1:34:28] Secret espionage warfare
[1:51:50] Trump vs. Biden Chaos


Powerful Insights From Andrew Bustamante:

“The way that you defeat extremism is by taking out the first step in the ladder.”

“When most people reference World War 3 happening, what they’re actually talking about is a nuclear war similar to how World War 2 ended. Wars evolve like people evolve, and if you’ve seen the evolution of technology you can imagine how much more advanced World War 3 would be than World War 2…”

“Human beings are wired to survive. We are not wired to thrive. We are wired to survive”

&quot;And of course, the United States is okay with that too, because it means there&#x27;s never going to be a military competitor in the North Atlantic Treaty Organization as a result. What does get to happen is those countries can take all the money that they would spend on military defense and channel it into intelligence operations.&quot;

&quot;So whatever happens, human beings will survive, will adapt, and will survive.&quot;

&quot;Ideology aside, if we want to protect American lives, we have to ensure the long term longevity, support and close relationships with the Israeli people and with the country of Israel. That is my official position.&quot;

&quot;When the United States cut off Russian bank accounts as part of their sanctions against Russia, and they cut off access to Russian funds that were denominated in euros and dollars, that was an economic warfare move.&quot;

&quot;Well, during those 20 years, while we were mastering the art of hunting terrorism, hunting terrorists in mountains in Pakistan and Afghanistan, what were our global power competitors doing? Was Russia engaged in the global war on terror? Was China involved in the global war on terror? So all the hundreds of billions of dollars that we spent in that war, we spent in a war that was a giant distraction for us, that gave our closest near peer competitors 20 years to invest their money and grow, to become a larger threat than we were even aware they were becoming.&quot;


Follow Andrew Bustamante:
Website: https://everydayspy.com/
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/everydayspy/
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/everydayspy 


Follow Me, Tom Bilyeu: 
Website: https://impacttheoryuniversity.com/ 
X: https://twitter.com/TomBilyeu
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tombilyeu/


If you want to dive deeper into my content, search through every episode, find specific topics I&#x27;ve covered, and ask me questions. Go to my Dexa page: https://dexa.ai/tombilyeu

Themes: Mindset, Finance, World Affairs, Health &amp; Productivity, Future &amp; Tech, Simulation Theory &amp; Physics, Dating &amp; Relationships]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.Vqam_Zu9UBE</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/Vqam_Zu9UBE.m4a" length="127864186" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/Vqam_Zu9UBE/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>18</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Saturday, April 27 2024 at 13:00:33</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mo Gawdat: This Is Causing 70% Of Heart Attacks In Young People! A WARNING for Workaholics! - The Diary Of A CEO</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Mo Gawdat is the former Chief Business Officer for Google X, the founder of ‘One Billion Happy’ foundation, and co-founder of ‘Unstressable’. He is the bestselling author of books such as, ‘Solve for Happy’, ‘Scary Smart’, and ‘That Little Voice in Your Head’.

00:00 Intro
02:01 Mo How Are You Doing?
07:08 Mo&#x27;s New Book &amp; The State Of The World
12:31 The Speed Of The World
17:14 Stress Is The New Addiction
26:41 Will I Lose Productivity Without Stress?
31:06 What is TONN? The Origin Of Stress
36:07 Upsetting People With Change &amp; Choosing To Put Ourselves First
43:31 What Is Loss Aversion?
50:43 The Noise Of Stress
01:01:38 How Do We Spot Our Own Stress?
01:04:49 Are We Really Too Busy?
01:12:18 Setting Limits &amp; Prioritising The Important Stuff
01:18:20 How Our Childhood Impact In Our Bias To Workaholism
01:22:22 Loss And How Long We Have Left
01:29:02 Passport Control Detention
01:29:49 How Do We Undo Stress
01:44:02 Work / Life Balance
01:44:52 The Impact Of AI
02:02:04 Being Successful And Balanced
02:16:20 Love &amp; Relationship Advice
02:26:17 Why Some People Don&#x27;t Find A Partner
02:34:22 Becoming Unstressable
02:40:15 Mo&#x27;s Family Heartache
02:44:53 What Would You Tell The First People You Loved


You can purchase Mo’s newest book, ‘Unstressable: A Practical Guide to Stress-Free Living’, available on 9th May 2024, here: https://amzn.to/3w6xG8h

Follow Mo:
Instagram - https://bit.ly/3w5VGIC
Twitter - https://bit.ly/3JwggoE
YouTube - https://bit.ly/3QlCUnt

My new book! &#x27;The 33 Laws Of Business &amp; Life&#x27; is out now - https://smarturl.it/DOACbook

Follow me:
https://beacons.ai/diaryofaceo

Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCGq-a57w-aPwyi3pW7XLiHw/join

Follow our Shorts channel for more content:
https://www.youtube.com/@TheDiaryofaCEOShorts

Sponsors:
Linkedin Ads: https://www.linkedin.com/doac24
Shopify: http://shopify.com/bartlett]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.IxVNR0Om-lA</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/IxVNR0Om-lA.m4a" length="168731255" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 15:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/IxVNR0Om-lA/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>19</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by The Diary Of A CEO published on Thursday, April 25 2024 at 07:00:07</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Don't Learn to Code, But Study This Instead..." says NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang - Goda Go</title>
      <description><![CDATA[I think a lot of people got it wrong what Jensen Huang, Co-Founder and CEO of NVIDIA was recently saying at the @WorldGovSummit . It is easy to grab a &quot;hot&quot; statement without considering the full context and the more important message about what we as humanity should focus more in the age of AI. 

I understand that most people don&#x27;t have time to sit through the full interview , thus my hope is that this video provides a better context without creating unnecessary additional anxiety that we are all so familiar now in the face of AI and rapid change.

Say Hi on Linkedin 👋: https://bit.ly/3EgMHVA
⭐️Visit us at synthminds.ai
⭐️Subscribe to our Weekly Newsletter: The Sync https://bit.ly/3ToRDjq

⬇️Resources mentioned in this video⬇️ 
⭐️Full Interview with NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang : https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8Pm2xEViNIo&amp;t=1221s

❤️Upcoming Uplimit courses: 
AI &amp; ChatGPT for Everyone (Cohort 3!!!): https://bit.ly/49bgDzZ
Explore all: https://bit.ly/47zoaHi

Thank you so much for watching and joining me on this journey! Let me know in the comments what you would like to see more of in the future. 
Bye!]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.vEd-LqBCONg</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/vEd-LqBCONg.m4a" length="11238312" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/vEd-LqBCONg/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>20</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Goda Go published on Monday, March  4 2024 at 13:49:47</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If You Want To Be SUCCESSFUL In Life, Master This ONE SKILL! | Simon Sinek - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Join our Discord community so you don’t miss out on all the amazing things we are working on - http://impacttheory.com/discord. Here you will get direct access to Tom and the team PLUS exclusive content, offers, and so much more. Jump on in and get started on becoming legendary!

Hey, if you&#x27;re a 6-7 figure business owner looking to scale your company, check out our Business Decision-Making Workshop. I will teach you the skills I used to scale Quest into a $1B company. 
Visit https://decision.impacttheory.com/apply?sl=ss to learn more and apply today!

Simon Sinek achieved international fame with the TED Talk “How great leaders inspire action” and his first book “Start With Why.” Now he is expanding his discussion of leadership and delving into the question of what has gone so wrong for businesses and their leaders. In this episode of Impact Theory with Tom Bilyeu, Simon Sinek goes deep into the subject of his newest work, “The Infinite Game.” He shares that most leaders don’t understand the infinite game they are in. Simon explains how our current business climate creates poor leaders, how to change that climate, and how to build the clarity and courage necessary to lead with an infinite mindset.

SHOW NOTES:

Simon defines an infinite game and advocates leading with an infinite mindset [3:27]
Simon advocates prioritizing people over revenue and profits [5:29]
Simon explains why prioritizing employees ends up leading to higher profits [8:01]
Simon describes why psychological safe spaces are necessary [11:03]
Simon explains why you can’t incentivize performance [13:02]
Simon describes economic history and how businesses became less people-friendly [14:36]
Simon advocates that leadership is a lifestyle and that it ought to be ethical [22:01]
Simon describes the importance of a just cause and how it differs from your “why” [26:21]
Simon explains why we have poor leaders [29:28]
Simon explains how to become a good leader [31:03]
Simon describes his belief that good leaders need worthy rivals [33:10]
Simon advocates the willingness to make profound strategic shifts to advance [36:26]
Simon explains how to build the courage to play the infinite game [40:27]
Simon advocates exhibiting empathy towards whoever is closest to you [44:45]
Simon and Tom discuss finding the language to describe the infinite game [47:12]
Simon advocates being the leader you wish you had [49:09]
Simon shares the impact he wants his book to have [50:49]

QUOTES:

“I’m tired of CEO’s telling me that, ‘Millennials these days don’t stick around.’ Well why would they if you don’t offer them any kind of loyalty back?” [18:35]
“Business is an infinite game. And when you play with a finite mindset lots of people suffer, including the companies they themselves are trying to build!” [21:00]
“Be the leader you wish you had.” [49:16]

FOLLOW:

WEBSITE: https://simonsinek.com
INSTAGRAM: http://bit.ly/2omV0ew
FACEBOOK: http://bit.ly/2nrOseS
TWITTER: http://bit.ly/2mNcoce


BOOKS MENTIONED IN THIS EPISODE:

“Start with Why” https://amzn.to/2p9Ntk1 [2:39]
“The Infinite Game” https://amzn.to/2p7LgFE [2:39]
“Leaders Eat Last” https://amzn.to/2p8i6pR [2:39]

IMPACT THEORY MERCHANDISE: Check out Impact Theory&#x27;s Merch Shop: http://bit.ly/ImpactTheoryShop]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.V2K4VqkfRaM</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/V2K4VqkfRaM.m4a" length="50633428" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/V2K4VqkfRaM/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>21</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Tuesday, October 15 2019 at 13:00:10</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking Truth About AI, Immortality, Civil War, Elon Musk &amp; Simulation Theory | Peter Diamandis - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[This episode is sponsored by Anthros. Head over to https://bit.ly/AnthrosImpact and get $200 off the office chair that promises to be the world&#x27;s most comfortable sitting experience.

This episode is sponsored by Viome. As a special offer to my viewers, Viome is offering $110 off your test. Go to https://bit.ly/ViomeImpact and use code IMPACT to save.

Brace yourself, as we explore these realms and the implications they hold for our future. My guest today, Peter Diamandis, the futurist to watch as all of these technologies advance with unimaginable speed, is going to blow your mind and help you imagine new possibilities and opportunities for your healthspan. 

Get ready to be inspired! Peter Diamandis’ visionary insights and groundbreaking work as a futurist, entrepreneur, and founder of XPRIZE Foundation has revolutionized industries and paved the way for advancements in technology, space exploration, and innovation. Prepare to be captivated by his expertise and learn from his remarkable accomplishments.

We delve deep into the shocking truths that will forever change the course of history with AI, quantum computing and biotech like you’ve never imagined.. 

I hope you’re ready for a disruption like never before, and if you’re not, this is your signal to start taking these things seriously so you’re not left behind in the disruption of the century. 

Chapter Markers:
[00:00] Introducing AI Simulation Theory
[00:33] Making Immortality A Reality
[19:20] Unraveling AI’s Acceleration
[45:20] Predicting Financial Markets with AI
[1:00:20] Health Opportunities You Can’t Miss
[1:27:30] 100 Year Rate of Change
[1:42:39] AI’s Age of Abundance 

Follow Peter Diamandis:
Website: https://www.diamandis.com/ 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/PeterDiamandis 
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/user/peterdiamandis 

Follow Me Tom Bilyeu: 
Website: https://impacttheoryuniversity.com/ 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/TomBilyeu 
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tombilyeu/]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.OSV7cxma6_s</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/OSV7cxma6_s.m4a" length="140883991" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/OSV7cxma6_s/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>22</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Tuesday, December 12 2023 at 14:00:24</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"You Should Be A Monster" | Jordan Peterson Motivation - WordToTheWise</title>
      <description><![CDATA[&quot;You don&#x27;t become safe by being castrated.&quot;
Try Audible&#x27;s free 30-day trial and enjoy 2 free audiobooks here: https://amzn.to/2MRvzxL
Check out Jordan Peterson&#x27;s latest book &quot;Beyond Order&quot;: https://amzn.to/3HEaTRh

▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂

➤➤Speaker:
Jordan B. Peterson
https://www.youtube.com/user/JordanPetersonVideos
https://jordanbpeterson.com/

2017 Personality 04/05: Heroic and Shamanic Initiations
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wLc_MC7NQek

➤➤More Videos:
How To Know Yourself | Jordan Peterson Life Advice
https://youtu.be/1gdHZ3wDiZc

CLEAN YOUR ROOM | Jordan Peterson Motivation
https://youtu.be/Vp9599kwnhM

It Always Paid Off | Jordan Peterson Life Advice
https://youtu.be/4f-Jg1Foqhs

LOOK WHERE YOU LEAST WANT TO | Jordan Peterson
https://youtu.be/LjIAzKo62MQ

How To Beat Fear And Anxiety | Jordan Peterson Life Advice
https://youtu.be/bb9g9mtDHZo
▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂▂

➤➤Transcript (partial):
Part of spiritual development is to recognize the Satanic tendencies that characterize you and to fully wrestle with them and to— and to integrate them. That&#x27;s the thing. It&#x27;s—it’s not so much to cast them away. It&#x27;s to transmute them, you know. And you can see the difference between people who&#x27;ve done that and people who haven&#x27;t, at least to some degree, because people who haven&#x27;t integrated the shadow at all are naive. And you can tell that when you look at them and you can tell that when you talk to them. And because they&#x27;re naive, they&#x27;re often resentful as well because they get taken advantage of. And someone who&#x27;s integrated that more, they&#x27;re dangerous in the—in the martial arts sort of way, which is they&#x27;re dangerous, but they don&#x27;t have to be. They don&#x27;t have to use it because their presence radiates implicit potential for havoc. And that&#x27;s really necessary. It&#x27;s one of the things that gives people self-respect. If you&#x27;re harmless, you&#x27;re not virtuous. You&#x27;re just harmless. You&#x27;re like a rabbit. A rabbit isn&#x27;t virtuous. It&#x27;s just... It just can&#x27;t do anything except get eaten! It&#x27;s not virtuous. If you&#x27;re a monster and you don&#x27;t act monstrously, then you&#x27;re virtuous. But you also have to be a monster. Well, you see this all the time. Harry Potter is like that, too. It&#x27;s like he&#x27;s— he&#x27;s flawed, he&#x27;s hurt. He&#x27;s got evil in him. He can talk to snakes, man. He breaks rules all the time. All the time. He&#x27;s not obedient at all. But, you know, he has a good reason for breaking the rules. And if he couldn&#x27;t break the rules, him and his little clique of rule breaking, you know, troublemakers, if they didn&#x27;t break the rules, they wouldn&#x27;t attain the highest goal. So it&#x27;s very peculiar, but it&#x27;s a very, very, very, very common mythological notion. You know, the hero has to be... The hero has to be a monster. But a controlled monster. Batman is like that, you know? I mean, it&#x27;s—it&#x27;s everywhere. It&#x27;s—it&#x27;s the story you always hear. If you&#x27;re going to be a fighter, you have to want to win and you have to want to hurt people. I mean, not for the sake of hurting them. That&#x27;s what makes you different than an evil person. But you have to have that capacity. You have to develop that. And, you know, that&#x27;s a step on the way to enlightenment, weirdly enough, because that isn&#x27;t what people think. People have been fed this diet of pablum, rights and impulsive freedom for so long. There&#x27;s just an absolute starvation for the other side of the story. There are no rights, technically speaking, without responsibilities. And all we&#x27;ve had for 60 years is a dialog about rights. Well, that leaves a hole on the other side of the story, and it&#x27;s a hole that— that’s in people&#x27;s hearts, essentially, because responsibility— well, perhaps that&#x27;s not more important than rights. Like I said, they&#x27;re they&#x27;re part and parcel of the same formula. But it&#x27;s in responsibility that most people find the meaning that sustains them through life. It&#x27;s not in happiness. It&#x27;s not in impulsive pleasure. Those things blow away at the first ill wind. But to adopt the responsibility for your own well-being and to try to put your family together and to try to serve your community and to try to seek for eternal truth and to live them— that&#x27;s the sort of thing that can ground you in— in your life enough so that you can withstand the difficulty of life. And when you tell people that, especially when you include yourself in the audience, let&#x27;s say, and you&#x27;re not finger waving from above, then everyone knows that it&#x27;s true. There&#x27;s been this attempt to identify masculine competence and— and power, let&#x27;s say, but mostly competence with tyranny. And that&#x27;s very, very hard on— on young men. It&#x27;s also hard on young women, for that matter. But it&#x27;s very helpful for people to hear that they should make themselves competent and dangerous and take their proper place in the world because it&#x27;s the alternative to being weak. And weak is not good. The people who shoot up the high schools, they&#x27;re weak. They&#x27;re weak. And life is a very difficult process. And you&#x27;re not prepared for it unless...]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.-gYpCIbZjUQ</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/-gYpCIbZjUQ.m4a" length="10668301" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 13:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/-gYpCIbZjUQ/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>23</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by WordToTheWise published on Wednesday, December  7 2022 at 13:00:00</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Peterson:  You need to be competent AND dangerous! - Jordan Peterson Clips</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Jordan Peterson talks about the importance of being competent AND dangerous. Watch John Stossel&#x27;s full interview with Jordan Peterson here - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p3368WAl0qM

#JordanPeterson]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.qwaLhSgi7q8</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/qwaLhSgi7q8.m4a" length="6189239" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/qwaLhSgi7q8/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>24</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Jordan Peterson Clips published on Thursday, April 28 2022 at 19:30:03</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The World Lied To You About Success, Money &amp; Power! - Escape Misery &amp; Suffering | Arthur Brooks - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Get Out of Your Head. Take Action Now! https://bit.ly/3M28lkA

Restart Your Life in 7 Days: https://bit.ly/3RgzVhi

“Life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness…”

You’ve heard this many times before, and yet have you ever wondered why life and liberty are automatically given and assumed while happiness isn’t . Why are millions of people around the world chasing happiness and very few ever “catch” it?

Arthur Brooks is a social scientist, Harvard professor, and bestselling author committed to helping people find success, happiness and deep meaning. He&#x27;s such a profound thought-leader in the space that he just released a book with Oprah called Build the Life You Want, The Art and Science of Getting Happier.

We explore a deeply thought-provoking conversation about the pursuit of happiness through progress, learning, and understanding. As simple as the idea of happiness seems on the surface, understanding the complexities of what it means to pursue it, relish tt, and define the meaning of it without attachment and dogmatic viewpoints escapes many people.

Some key areas we dive hard and deep on that I think you will find so interesting are:
1) The role of progress in human flourishing
2) The danger of being attached and dogmatic with your beliefs
3) The importance not allowing your views to define you

What I enjoyed most about our conversation was how far we explored and unpacked in areas that are potentially controversial topics like religious beliefs, political differences, and family schisms. Get ready to challenge your base assumptions and view existential threats from new angles.


ARTHUR BROOKS QUOTES:

“The idea that you can be blissful and happy all the time is not just unrealistic, it&#x27;s unhealthy. It would be terrible if you were happy all the time.”

“If you don&#x27;t defend your positions, if you admit to the possibility that you&#x27;re not right, that you learn and you update when people say things that you think are crazy, you say, tell me more that you&#x27;re actually going to get better.”

“Any time you use your values as a weapon, you&#x27;ve denigrated their moral content. You&#x27;ve eviscerated the effectiveness of your approach. But if you use your values as a gift it might not always be taken in a charitable way.”

“Each of us is an entrepreneur in the startup of our lives. That&#x27;s what really matters. And what we need is to always have a clear intention…”

“The best thing that you can possibly do is to think about the emotions that you&#x27;re feeling, what they mean and how best to use them.” 

“All the things we really want in life. All of our deep desires are complex. All of our solutions are complicated, and we&#x27;re throwing complicated solutions at complex problems and we&#x27;re not getting happier.”

“They&#x27;re not entrepreneurial in the part of life that matters the most, which is their heart.”

““The first one is that there is meaning. You need to find it and live up to it.”


Follow Arthur Brooks:
Website: https://arthurbrooks.com/ 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/arthurbrooks 
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/@arthurbrooks123 
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/arthurcbrooks/]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.B8O6aTHBBTY</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/B8O6aTHBBTY.m4a" length="161776066" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 13:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/B8O6aTHBBTY/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>25</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Tuesday, September 12 2023 at 13:00:09</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Peterson: Life, Death, Power, Fame, and Meaning | Lex Fridman Podcast #313 - Lex Fridman</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Jordan Peterson is a psychologist, lecturer, podcast host, and author. Please support this podcast by checking out our sponsors:
- Notion: https://notion.com/startups to get up to $1000 off team plan
- InsideTracker: https://insidetracker.com/lex to get 20% off
- Eight Sleep: https://www.eightsleep.com/lex and use code LEX to get special savings
- Blinkist: https://blinkist.com/lex to get 25% off premium

EPISODE LINKS:
Jordan&#x27;s Twitter: https://twitter.com/jordanbpeterson
Jordan&#x27;s Website: https://jordanbpeterson.com
Jordan&#x27;s Books:
Beyond Order: https://amzn.to/3T4LRBw
12 Rules for Life: https://amzn.to/3c4sqYF
Maps of Meaning: https://amzn.to/3A1Ods2
Websites mentioned:
Essay App: https://essay.app
Self Authoring: https://selfauthoring.com
Peterson Academy: https://petersonacademy.com

PODCAST INFO:
Podcast website: https://lexfridman.com/podcast
Apple Podcasts: https://apple.co/2lwqZIr
Spotify: https://spoti.fi/2nEwCF8
RSS: https://lexfridman.com/feed/podcast/
Full episodes playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLrAXtmErZgOdP_8GztsuKi9nrraNbKKp4
Clips playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLrAXtmErZgOeciFP3CBCIEElOJeitOr41

OUTLINE:
0:00 - Introduction
0:47 - Dostoevsky
11:48 - God
19:58 - Science
32:21 - Death
35:15 - Elon Musk
39:13 - Global Crisis
51:26 - Dangerous ideologies
1:02:40 - Justin Trudeau
1:16:46 - War in Ukraine
1:34:14 - Day in the life
2:10:18 - How to think
2:25:26 - Depression
2:33:33 - Advice for young people
2:47:22 - Russian literature
2:59:10 - Meaning of life

SOCIAL:
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/lexfridman
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lexfridman
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/lexfridman
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/lexfridman
- Medium: https://medium.com/@lexfridman
- Reddit: https://reddit.com/r/lexfridman
- Support on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/lexfridman]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.sY8aFSY2zv4</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/sY8aFSY2zv4.m4a" length="178229142" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 19:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/sY8aFSY2zv4/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>26</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Lex Fridman published on Friday, August 19 2022 at 15:56:20</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Altman: OpenAI, GPT-5, Sora, Board Saga, Elon Musk, Ilya, Power &amp; AGI | Lex Fridman Podcast #419 - Lex Fridman</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Sam Altman is the CEO of OpenAI, the company behind GPT-4, ChatGPT, Sora, and many other state-of-the-art AI technologies. Please support this podcast by checking out our sponsors:
- Cloaked: https://cloaked.com/lex and use code LexPod to get 25% off
- Shopify: https://shopify.com/lex to get $1 per month trial
- BetterHelp: https://betterhelp.com/lex to get 10% off
- ExpressVPN: https://expressvpn.com/lexpod to get 3 months free

TRANSCRIPT:
https://lexfridman.com/sam-altman-2-transcript

EPISODE LINKS:
Sam&#x27;s X: https://x.com/sama
Sam&#x27;s Blog: https://blog.samaltman.com/
OpenAI&#x27;s X: https://x.com/OpenAI
OpenAI&#x27;s Website: https://openai.com
ChatGPT Website: https://chat.openai.com/
Sora Website: https://openai.com/sora
GPT-4 Website: https://openai.com/research/gpt-4

PODCAST INFO:
Podcast website: https://lexfridman.com/podcast
Apple Podcasts: https://apple.co/2lwqZIr
Spotify: https://spoti.fi/2nEwCF8
RSS: https://lexfridman.com/feed/podcast/
Full episodes playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLrAXtmErZgOdP_8GztsuKi9nrraNbKKp4
Clips playlist: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLrAXtmErZgOeciFP3CBCIEElOJeitOr41

OUTLINE:
0:00 - Introduction
1:05 - OpenAI board saga
18:31 - Ilya Sutskever
24:40 - Elon Musk lawsuit
34:32 - Sora
44:23 - GPT-4
55:32 - Memory &amp; privacy
1:02:36 - Q*
1:06:12 - GPT-5
1:09:27 - $7 trillion of compute
1:17:35 - Google and Gemini
1:28:40 - Leap to GPT-5
1:32:24 - AGI
1:50:57 - Aliens

SOCIAL:
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/lexfridman
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lexfridman
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/lexfridman
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/lexfridman
- Medium: https://medium.com/@lexfridman
- Reddit: https://reddit.com/r/lexfridman
- Support on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/lexfridman]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.jvqFAi7vkBc</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/jvqFAi7vkBc.m4a" length="111828453" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 19:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/jvqFAi7vkBc/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>27</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Lex Fridman published on Monday, March 18 2024 at 15:03:19</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Spy: "Leave The USA Before 2030!" Why You Shouldn't Trust Your Gut! - Andrew Bustamante - The Diary Of A CEO</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Andrew Bustamante is a former covert CIA intelligence officer and US Air Force combat veteran. He is the founder of EverydaySpy, an online education platform that teaches real-world international espionage techniques that can be used in everyday life.

00:00 Intro
02:47 Your Time At The CIA
03:15 What Is The CIA?
03:57 You&#x27;ve Got It Wrong About Spies
06:43 Applying Real Spy Skills To Overcome Any Barrier In Our Lives
08:13 How To Manipulate People
18:15 The Psychological Profile Of A CIA Agent
21:13 I Held The Key To Nuclear Missiles
23:15 It Was A Horrible Job
25:00 Would You Have You Pressed The Nuclear Button?
27:18 The CIA Message That Changed My Life
29:13 The Interview Process For The CIA
31:31 How Did You Feel When You Received That Letter?
33:54 Did The CIA Tell You To Cut Off From Your Social Circle?
34:44 Your Ethnicity Factor To Be Recruited By The CIA
36:03 Do You Have To Change Your Identity?
37:14 How Expensive Is To Train A CIA Agent?
37:21 What&#x27;s The CIA Training Scheme?
38:04 Do They Show You How To Kill?
39:06 How You Teach The Art Of Lying
41:00 Body Language &amp; Lying
42:46 Demystifying Lying Signs
45:44 How To Tell If Someone Is Lying
47:34 Human Psychology
50:32 The Essence Of Manipulation
52:09 How To Find Someone&#x27;s Ideology To Manipulate Them
56:12 Have You Changed The Way You Look At The World?
01:00:01 Perception vs Perceptive
01:01:59 Leaning Into Objective vs Subjective Feelings
01:03:25 How To Train Yourself To Apply Rational Objective Perspective
01:05:54 Your Business Success
01:09:01 What Is SADRAT?
01:11:07 Change The Game When Selling Your Products
01:13:13 What Is Espionage?
01:14:08 What Is Our Secret Life?
01:18:16 How To Enter Someone&#x27;s Secret Life
01:23:33 How To Apply It To Business
01:26:19 Adapting To Change Faster Than Your Opponent
01:29:18 Were There Times Your Life Was At Threat?
01:31:43 Sexpionage, What Is It?
01:33:49 Disguise, Did You Ever Do It?
01:38:44 Do CIA Agents Get Trained To Not Feel Fear &amp; Anxiety?
01:41:23 How Do They Train You To Slow Down Your Emotional Brain?
01:47:28 Your Wife &amp; You Leaving The CIA
01:48:55 America Is Going Through A Hard Period
01:54:15 What&#x27;s The Advice For Everyone To Make That Change?
01:56:27 How Does Your Identity Stop You From Evolving?
01:57:39 What Is Something You Used To Believe That You No Longer Do?

Want to learn more from Andrew?
Find your Spy Superpower: https://everydayspy.com/spyquiz
Explore Spy School: https://everydayspy.com/
Join the podcast: https://youtube.com/@EverydaySpyPodcast

Follow Andrew
Twitter - https://bit.ly/49AI9qT
Instagram - https://bit.ly/4bTOIqf
YouTube - https://bit.ly/3IkEhOY

Follow our Shorts channel for more content:
https://www.youtube.com/@TheDiaryofaCEOShorts

Join this channel to get access to perks:
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCGq-a57w-aPwyi3pW7XLiHw/join

Follow me:
https://beacons.ai/diaryofaceo

Sponsors:
Whoop: https://join.whoop.com/en-uk/CEO]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.QVVe2rCHtN0</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/QVVe2rCHtN0.m4a" length="118776067" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 17:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/QVVe2rCHtN0/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>28</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by The Diary Of A CEO published on Monday, March  4 2024 at 08:00:55</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Justify Your Prices. Do This Instead. - The Futur</title>
      <description><![CDATA[When prospects challenge your pricing, how do you respond? Chris Do shares an empowering new approach to handling this tricky situation with finesse.

Learn a simple yet highly effective method to reframe the conversation in your favor, and discover how to establish trust and authority by guiding prospects through prioritizing their must-haves.

FREE Resources here: https://thefutur.com/free-resources

🚀 Futur Accelerator
The step-by-step blueprint and coaching program designed to get your creative business off the ground:
https://thefutur.com/accelerator

🥇 Futur Pro 
The professional creative community designed to grow your personal brand, your business, and your network:
https://thefutur.com/pro

✍️ Other Courses, Templates, and Tools:
https://thefutur.com/shop

🎙 The Futur Podcast:
https://thefutur.com/podcast

Recommended books, tools, music, resources, typefaces &amp; more: 
https://thefutur.com/recommendations

Music by Epidemic Sound:
http://share.epidemicsound.com/thefutur

Shorts Playlist: 
https://www.youtube.com/@thefutur/shorts

We love getting your letters. Send them here:
The Futur c/o Chris Do
556 S. Fair Oaks Ave. #34
Pasadena CA 91105

*By making a purchase through any of our affiliate links, we receive a very small commission at no extra cost to you. This helps us on our mission to provide quality education to you. Thank you.

--
Host: Chris Do
Producer: Mark Contreras
Cinematographers/Editors: Stewart Schuster @RodrigoTasca &amp;  @Tascastudios  MOCS Media]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.Abi8kwkfZbA</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/Abi8kwkfZbA.m4a" length="8591104" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/Abi8kwkfZbA/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>29</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by The Futur published on Thursday, October 19 2023 at 14:00:05</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branding &amp; Marketing In The Age Of AI with Seth Godin - Brand Master Academy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[In this episode of the Brand Master podcast, Marketing legend Seth Godin joins us to discuss Branding &amp; Marketing in the age of AI. 

The fusion of artificial intelligence (AI) with branding and marketing is not just inevitable but essential for those looking to stay ahead. 

In this revelatory episode of the Brandmaster Podcast, we delve deep into the transformative power of AI and its unprecedented impact on the marketing landscape, as shared by the legendary Seth Godin, a luminary in branding and marketing.

Discover how AI is reshaping the future of branding and marketing, as we engage in a thought-provoking conversation with Seth Godin. Learn why integrating AI into your daily marketing practices is non-negotiable for future success.

For more insights on brand strategy and to connect with a community of dedicated brand strategists, visit BrandMasterAcademy.com.

Stay tuned for upcoming episodes packed with practical, actionable advice on branding. 

Your reviews and thoughts are invaluable to us – they help us grow and continue providing greater value to our listeners.

#sethgodin #marketingai #brandingai #brandingvsmarketingai


----------------✅ FREE BRAND STRATEGY RESOURCES ✅--------------------

✅  FREE PRO BRAND STRATEGY BLUEPRINT: 
https://brandmasteracademy.com/brand-strategy-blueprint/?utm_source=youtube&amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;utm_term=vid-desc&amp;utm_content=&amp;utm_campaign=bms


✅  BECOME A BRAND STRATEGIST
Our flagship training “Brand Master Secrets” - Everything you need to become an in-demand brand strategist, raise your expert profile and grow your branding revenue and business.
https://brandmasteracademy.com/brand-master-secrets/?utm_source=youtube&amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;utm_term=vid-desc&amp;utm_content=&amp;utm_campaign=bms


✅  FACILITATE BRAND STRATEGY WORKSHOPS LIKE A PRO
Learn the techniques, systems and delivery tools to develop brands WITH your clients, to build brands they believe in and are invested in.
https://brandmasteracademy.com/brand-master-workshops/


✅  INSIDE BRAND MASTER SECRETS
https://brandmasteracademy.com/brand-master-secrets/?utm_source=youtube&amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;utm_term=vid-desc&amp;utm_content=&amp;utm_campaign=bms


✅  BRAND MASTER ACADEMY
The brand strategist training ground


https://brandmasteracademy.com/?utm_source=youtube&amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;utm_term=vid-desc&amp;utm_content=&amp;utm_campaign=bms


--------------- ✴️ LEARN FROM OTHER STRATEGISTS IN THE COMMUNITY ✴️ --------------------


✴️✴️  BRAND MASTER ACADEMY ON SOCIAL
Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/stephenhouraghan/
Facebook - https://www.facebook.com/pg/brandmasteracademy
Linkedin - https://www.linkedin.com/in/stephen-houraghan
Youtube - https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCBFWrMRo37OVLM2l1pWnH7w?sub_confirmation=1
Twitter - https://twitter.com/BrandMasterAcad

✴️✴️  JOIN THE FACEBOOK COMMUNITY
https://www.facebook.com/groups/brandmasteracademy/
Join in the conversation with other experienced and budding brand strategists to enhance your brand-building systems.

✴️✴️ EXCLUSIVE TIPS &amp; TECHNIQUES
https://brandmasteracademy.com/subscribe/
Get on the list for exclusive brand strategy tips and techniques


---------------- 🎧 LISTEN TO THE PODCAST 🎧 --------------------

🎧🎧 LISTEN TO THE BRAND MASTER PODCAST
https://brandmasteracademy.com/brand-master-podcast/?utm_source=youtube&amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;utm_term=vid-desc&amp;utm_content=&amp;utm_campaign=bms


----------------🙏  SUPPORT THE CHANNEL 🙏--------------------

AFFILIATE LINKS
Support Brand Master Academy by purchasing through our affiliate links.
We get a small commission with no extra cost to you.

🙏🙏  AMAZON | https://amzn.to/30JtFmU
🙏🙏  DESIGN CUTS | https://bit.ly/3cyGPso
🙏🙏  EPIDEMIC SOUND | https://bit.ly/3cyGPso
🙏🙏  WEBFLOW | https://webflow.grsm.io/bma
🙏🙏  CONVERTKIT | https://convertkit.com/?lmref=R3KyAw
🙏🙏  AWEBER | https://bit.ly/3rWpzDR]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.SJPUm4RAtvA</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/SJPUm4RAtvA.m4a" length="40752324" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 17:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/SJPUm4RAtvA/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>30</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Brand Master Academy published on Tuesday, February 13 2024 at 11:29:35</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Ng: Opportunities in AI - 2023 - Stanford Online</title>
      <description><![CDATA[This discussion took place on July 26, 2023, at Cemex Auditorium, Stanford University, and was hosted by the Stanford Graduate School of Business.

This talk covers:
Trends in AI Technologies and Tools
Supervised Learning
Generative AI
The Adoption of AI
Opportunities in AI
Process for Building Startups
AI Risks and Social Impact

Explore the essentials of machine learning and develop practical skills to implement AI applications in this beginner-friendly program: 
https://www.coursera.org/specializations/machine-learning-introduction]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.5p248yoa3oE</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/5p248yoa3oE.m4a" length="35839313" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/5p248yoa3oE/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>31</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Stanford Online published on Tuesday, August 29 2023 at 22:49:19</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Peterson Canceled: Warning On Good vs Evil, God, WW3, Andrew Tate, Porn &amp; Men Feeling Lost! - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Disclosure: This episode was sponsored by Ground News. This post may contain affiliate links or links to the sponsor’s website. If you purchase an item using this affiliate link, Impact Theory may receive commission. Go to https://bit.ly/GroundImpact to see through misleading media narratives. Subscribe through my link to get 40% off unlimited access this month only.

You can try Aura for free for two weeks at https://bit.ly/3KJd7mC. The Smart, Simple Way To Stay Safe Online.

Can humanity ever truly overcome evil? Can personal responsibility truly shape destiny in an interconnected world? Can society survive without traditional masculine virtues? Consider this your warning…

Dr. Jordan B. Peterson is a renowned psychologist, author, and online educator here to help us navigate the complex layers of thought, emotion, and spirit that compose the human condition. A Canadian clinical psychologist by profession, Jordan carved a unique path that intertwined academic rigor with deep reflections on morality, meaning, and belief. 

In today’s thought-provoking episode, Jordan is answering deep questions about life, purpose, and the potential for human transformation.

We touch on: 
- The line between good and evil
- Healthy vs. toxic masculinity
- Social media&#x27;s role in society&#x27;s rapid transformation
- Personal responsibility and the pursuit of meaning
- Cultural castration of men
- Human suffering and wrestling with God
- The challenges of conveying wisdom through religious narratives
- The OnlyFans dynamic 
- Genuine religious pursuit vs. exploitation for tyrannical ends
- Victimhood narratives and moral superiority

From the depths of human nature and the potential for totalitarianism, to the power of religious and philosophical insights in understanding the complexities of life, Jordan and I delve into the complex landscape of human psychology, ideology, and the search for meaning. 

Don’t miss this journey into the heart of what it means to be human, and confront your beliefs, fears, and moral compass in this episode of Impact Theory.


Chapter Markers:

[0:00] When Will the Doomsday Clock Strike Midnight? 
[15:06] The Canary in the Coal Mine
[31:01] The Runaway Cycle of Transformation
[44:03] Wrestling with God
[59:27] Separation of the Wheat from the Chaff
[1:11:47] Cracking Human Intelligence with LLMs 
[1:33:49] Message from Culture to “Castrate Yourself”
[1:51:02] Predators, oppressors, and power


Powerful Insights From Dr. Jordan B. Peterson:
&quot;If you don&#x27;t believe in something like the ultimate reality of evil, it&#x27;s just the Nazis went about things a slightly different way. Who&#x27;s to say what&#x27;s right or wrong?&quot;

&quot;It&#x27;s no wonder that we believe in the union of diversity when we believe that a man can be a woman. If we believe those things, there&#x27;s nothing we won&#x27;t swallow, no camel too big to go down our throats, no totalitarian lie we won&#x27;t rush to embody.&quot;

“There&#x27;s a vertical axis of orientation upward towards God, mediated by tradition, and there&#x27;s a horizontal axis that&#x27;s part of the ongoing conversation and consensus of the moment.&quot;

&quot;And so the world of images is going to have the same networked structure as the world of words that the LLMs have modeled. Soon the LLms will be able to model the world of images and soon they&#x27;ll be able to lay them on top of one another.&quot;

&quot;...everything you give away, you&#x27;ll get back if you give it away in the right spirit.&quot;

&quot;You give more than you&#x27;re called upon to give, even to your enemies. Why? Because there is no better strategy than that by any stretch of the imagination…How could you possibly put anything in a more solid bank than in the goodwill you generated in the embodied imaginations of other people? That&#x27;s the kingdom.&quot;

Follow Dr. Jordan B Peterson:
Website: https://www.jordanbpeterson.com/
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/c/jordanpetersonvideos
X: https://twitter.com/jordanbpeterson
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/jordan.b.peterson/
Preorder “We Who Wrestle with God”: https://www.jordanbpeterson.com/books/

Follow Me, Tom Bilyeu: 
Website: https://impacttheoryuniversity.com/ 
X: https://twitter.com/TomBilyeu
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tombilyeu/

If you want to dive deeper into my content, search through every episode, find specific topics I&#x27;ve covered, and ask me questions. Go to my Dexa page: https://dexa.ai/tombilyeu

Themes: Mindset, Finance, World Affairs, Health &amp; Productivity, Future &amp; Tech, Simulation Theory &amp; Physics, Dating &amp; Relationships]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.g6VNAM58a_U</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/g6VNAM58a_U.m4a" length="130438634" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 21:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/g6VNAM58a_U/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>32</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Tuesday, February 20 2024 at 14:00:26</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>URGENT: Ex-Google CBO says AI is now IMPOSSIBLE to stop with Mo Gawdat - James Laughlin</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DON&#x27;T GET LEFT BEHIND IN 2024! Download the 11 Visionary Leadership Tactics for 2024 for FREE here - https://www.jjlaughlin.com/offers/2wBnEQEH/checkout

-Grab my FREE Leader’s Toolkit to help you supercharge your life and career in 7 steps - jjlaughlin.com/toolkit

-Join the waitlist to be at my High Performance Leadership Event here - https://www.jjlaughlin.com/leadershipnewzealand 

-Click here to Become a VIP supporter of Lead On Purpose: https://www.buzzsprout.com/1583287/support

If you would like to help James continue to bring on world-class guests, please consider making a small recurring donation to cover the back end, admin and editing costs. For many years, James has dedicated countless hours to the show and would LOVE to continue bringing you global thought leaders.

Thank you for your support. It is greatly appreciated.

With much gratitude.


————————————————————————————

————————————————————————————


I have never put out an urgent episode before. I recorded this conversation 5 days ago with the incredible Mo Gawdat. After our conversation, I realised how urgent this information is and how critical it is that we are all aware of the super-intelligence of AI.

Mo Gawdat is the Former Chief Business Officer for Google X, an AI expert, a best-selling author and a passionate podcaster.

Mo spoke to me about AI. Most people bury their head in the sand when it comes to this topic, Mo is trying to change that. He believes that AI can be used for good, however we all need to work together to make that happen. 

This episode is incredibly important. If you have any loved ones or people you care about, make sure you send this on to them. I urge you to listen carefully and then take action.

Subscribe to Mo’s podcast : Slo Mo here - https://podcasts.apple.com/nz/podcast/slo-mo-a-podcast-with-mo-gawdat/id1508914142

Purchase a copy of his books here - https://www.mogawdat.com/books

Learn more about Mo here - https://www.mogawdat.com


——————————————————


Connect with James:

- Website: https://www.jjlaughlin.com 

- YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC6GETJbxpgulYcYc6QAKLHA 

- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/JamesLaughlinOfficial 

- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/jameslaughlinofficial/ 

- Apple Podcast: https://podcasts.apple.com/nz/podcast/life-on-purpose-with-james-laughlin/id1547874035 

- Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/show/3WBElxcvhCHtJWBac3nOlF?si=hotcGzHVRACeAx4GvybVOQ

- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jameslaughlincoaching/

#AI #ArtificialIntelligence #ChatGPTprompts #MoGawdat]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.fDHvUviV8nk</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/fDHvUviV8nk.m4a" length="91120998" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/fDHvUviV8nk/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>33</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by James Laughlin published on Wednesday, September 13 2023 at 14:23:51</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing a Customer-Centric Business Model - Harvard Innovation Labs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Simply defined, a business model is how you deliver value to customers and how you make money in return. The most successful business models capture value in concert with the customer. In this session, originally presented in-person at the Harvard Innovation Labs, you’ll learn how to do just that. Michael Skok, founding partner at Underscore VC, will share how to identify your core business value and align your business model to your customer’s success. 

About the Speaker: 

Michael Skok is a founding partner at Underscore VC, a Boston-based firm investing in bold B2B software founders. Since starting his first software business as a teenager, Michael has spent 21 years as an entrepreneur and the past 18 years as a venture investor. During this time, he has founded, worked with, and invested in startups, and created thousands of jobs and billions of dollars of value.  

As an entrepreneur and an investor, Michael has focused on breakthrough technologies and disruptive business models including Open Source, Cloud, IoT, and emerging domains such as Blockchain, Virtual/Augmented Reality, and Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning. He has served on or is active on many private and public boards such as Acquia, Demandware (now a Salesforce company), Mautic (acquired by Acquia in 2019), Salsify, and Zaius. He has also held leadership roles in many industry groups such as the Software Publishers Association, where he served as chairman for many years. 

In 2015, Michael co-founded Underscore VC to help founders create enduring companies through the power of community. He has a passion for helping the next generation of entrepreneurs succeed by not only backing them with capital but bringing the resources and commitment of an aligned community around them to propel their success. To help achieve this, he has mentored and taught for over 10 years at Harvard University, where he is an Entrepreneur in Residence, and created the Startup Secrets series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.L1Km-hJt-uI</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/L1Km-hJt-uI.m4a" length="80646602" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 06:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/L1Km-hJt-uI/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>34</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Harvard Innovation Labs published on Saturday, March 25 2023 at 13:00:12</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Spy On WW3, Jeffrey Epstein, Israel-Hamas, AI &amp; Social Media Brainwashing | Andrew Bustamante - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Transform Your Life in 90 Days: Take The Impact 90 Challenge  https://bit.ly/47kCfrZ

This episode is sponsored by Aura. You can try Aura for free for two weeks at https://bit.ly/3KJd7mC. The Smart, Simple Way To Stay Safe Online.

We&#x27;re delving deep into the unsettling realities of our chaotic world with former CIA spy, Andrew Bustamante. As we face an increasingly complex and confusing era, understanding the tactics and strategies used to manipulate public opinion has never been more crucial.

In this episode, we examine the distressing prospect of America turning against itself and the increasing potential for war. Andrew shares his ideas on how external attacks on our system could ironically unify us, but also how these threats are being weaponized to destabilize America. We look at the concept of World War 3 and it not being fought on traditional battlefields, but through proxy wars and influence campaigns that target our resources, dominance, and global standing.

It’s near impossible that you are not impacted on various levels by the role of the internet in accelerating the velocity of information. We’re in a time where enabling psychological manipulation on an unprecedented scale is happening right now as we speak.

How will you protect yourself? Will you learn how to think through novel problems and utilize opposing narratives against each other to discover the truth?

By the end of this episode, you’ll learn how to anchor yourself, make clear-headed decisions, and avoid the trap of emotional decision-making. In listening to both sides of the political spectrum and finding common ground, we can cut through the &#x27;fog of war&#x27; and discern truth from noise.

Andrew Bustamante delivers invaluable insights from his time as a CIA spy, offering a unique perspective on the truth about Jeffrey Epstein, conspiracy theories, porn and sexpionage that will shock you!

Ready for a mind-blowing episode? Subscribe, like, comment, and share to help us spread these vital conversations.

Find your Spy Superpower with Andrew Here: https://everydayspy.com/spyquiz   

Chapter Markers:
[00:00] Introductions to WW3 &amp; Civil War 
[14:20] Decoding Chaos: Thinking Strategies
[57:30] Target People With Truth 
[1:07:51] Unpacking Israel-Hamas 
[2:15:10] 2024 Presidential Election
[2:33:00] Social Media Brainwashing
[2:44:07] Epstein CIA Conspiracy Theories
[2:56:06] Falling for Sexpionage

Powerful Insights From Andrew Bustamante:

“At our core we are a fighting culture. It’s one of our biggest flaws and it’s one of our biggest strengths.”

“Emotional decision making is what the human brain wants to do, [...] because emotional decisions require less cognitive ability, less calories, less time and is easier…”

“Truth includes facts and beliefs, and facts excludes beliefs.”

“The way that you defeat extremism is by taking out the first step in the ladder.”

“When most people reference World War 3 happening, what they’re actually talking about is a nuclear war similar to how World War 2 ended. Wars evolve like people evolve, and if you’ve seen the evolution of technology you can imagine how much more advanced World War 3 would be than World War 2…”

Follow Andrew Bustamante:
Website: https://everydayspy.com/ 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/EverydaySpy 
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/everydayspy 
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/everydayspy/ 

Follow Me, Tom Bilyeu: 
Website: https://impacttheoryuniversity.com/ 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/TomBilyeu 
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tombilyeu/]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.l46oWMu3b9M</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/l46oWMu3b9M.m4a" length="185415126" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/l46oWMu3b9M/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>35</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Friday, January  5 2024 at 13:00:43</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI is a Bigger THREAT Than Nuclear Weapons | Mo Gawdat - Rob Moore</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Rob is joined by former Google X Officer and Artificial Intelligence expert Mo Gawdat. Rob and Mo reveal the dangers of AI and the meaning of life.

Get Rob’s digital financial toolkit here for free to make manage &amp; multiple more money 
https://bit.ly/rbtoolkityt

Subscribe to my other YouTube channels:

Moore Money Secrets
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC9m9uR_gfIlh-wGiK5vg63Q 

Disruptors Shorts
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCo73qQ2qcm2q1ldQhKee3jg

Moore Money Secrets Shorts 
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWvEm92RKHqvtC8orAeLKMQ

Become a community member for EXCLUSIVE content👇👇
If you want the raw, uncut editions of Disruptors interviews; content too controversial to publish on YouTube, you can gain instant access to dozen of episodes on Rob.team: http://rob.team 

Rob.team is a private, exclusive members content area for anyone wanting to start or scale a business, get better financial knowledge, gain access to masterclass on building multiple streams of income, digital assets, online &amp; information income &amp; access a disruptive entrepreneur community of 5,000+ members building a movement against political control &amp; towards personal &amp; financial freedom. It costs 1/3 of a Netflix subscription, you can cancel anytime with no contract &amp; there is 100s of hours of instantly accessible masterclass content. It’s all here: http://rob.team

Disruptors Podcast Links 
https://linktr.ee/robmoore
☑ iTunes: http://itunes.apple.com/podcast/tde/id1076679649
☑ Stitcher: http://stitcher.com/s?fid=81510

The world is on the edge of a revolution. Wealth, power &amp; information are being disrupted. 
Mainstream media is dying. Your freedom is being challenged. Your money is being debased.

The unrest is palpable. #Disruptors &amp; Rob Moore asks the questions others dare not to ask. Disruptive &amp; diverse guests speak out on topical world issues &amp; their areas of success &amp; influence.

Having evolved from the Disruptive Entrepreneur, the focus started with entrepreneurs, billionaires; business &amp; money related interviews &amp; solo Rob’s Rants. As there world has changed, Disruptors has evolved to diverse, global movers, shakers &amp; change makers who stand out &amp; speak up. 

Unscripted. Unedited. Unfiltered. 

Education, inspiration &amp; a fight for freedom. 
If you don’t risk anything, you risk everything]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.jVO7sIQl0e4</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/jVO7sIQl0e4.m4a" length="69050526" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 18:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/jVO7sIQl0e4/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>36</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Rob Moore published on Monday, February  5 2024 at 18:30:36</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevTalles PodCast - 141: Problemas comunes a los que se enfrentan los desarrolladores de software - Fernando Herrera</title>
      <description><![CDATA[🖥️ En este episodio quiero que tengamos presente 14 de los problemas más comunes a los que nos enfrentaremos: cuando estemos trabajando en el #Desarrollo de una #Aplicación.
#Software

📚 Puedes acceder a mi curso actualizado de Angular aquí: https://fernando-herrera.com/#/search/Angular:%20De%20cero%20a%20experto

🅰️ La nueva sintaxis no es común aún, por lo que si tienen que trabajar en aplicaciones de Angular, lo harán de la forma tradicional con módulos. Además esta versión es retro-compatible, y podemos ir progresivamente usando las nuevas características. Estos añadidos al framework buscan hacerlo moderno, más rápido y amigable. Al final, esta nueva sintaxis es como cuando React propuso los hooks y functional components en lugar de clases, o cuando Vue.Js introdujo el Composition API sobre el options API. 

👉🏻  Y puedes obtener Acceso Anticipado a mi curso actualizado de Next como beneficio de la Suscripción DevTalles PRO: https://cursos.devtalles.com/courses/nextjs#precios

También puedes adquirir el curso anterior, y cuando se finalice la grabación en unos meses, obtendrás el update gratuito en ambas plataformas:  https://fernando-herrera.com/#/search/Next

🎁 En DevTalles exclusivamente: tendrás el beneficio añadido de conservar tanto el curso original de Next, como el nuevos actualizado que se están construyendo.

🔗 Mi Web Personal: https://fernando-herrera.com
🎙️ Mi Podcast: https://anchor.fm/fernando-her85
👥 Mi X / Twitter: https://twitter.com/Fernando_Her85
👨🏻‍🏫 Perfil de instructor | Udemy: https://www.udemy.com/user/550c38655e...
👨🏻‍💻 {d/t} DevTalles: https://cursos.devtalles.com/
👨🏻‍🎓 {d/t} DevTalles LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/company/devt...
📱 {d/t} DevTalles X / Twitter: https://twitter.com/DevTalles
🚀 {d/t} DevTalles Comunidad Discord: https://discord.gg/pBjEVYTC7t

💻 #Programacion #Development #Developer #FernandoHerrera #DevTalles #Fullstack #OnlineLearning #professor #instructor]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.hjB5Jsi9Lt8</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://uuebcast.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/hjB5Jsi9Lt8.m4a" length="36765289" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 16:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/hjB5Jsi9Lt8/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>37</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Fernando Herrera published on Sunday, November 19 2023 at 12:00:10</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>¿Cómo convertirse en HACKER? | Con @s4vitar 🔴 HackerLIVE#29 - MoureDev by Brais Moure</title>
      <description><![CDATA[¿Quieres aprender ciberseguridad y convertirte en hacker? 
S4vitar, hacker y divulgador, nos habla sobre hacking ético, ciberseguridad, y cómo podemos llegar a seguir sus pasos.

► SIGUE A S4VITAR:
• @s4vitar 
• https://twitch.tv/s4vitaar
• https://twitter.com/S4vitar

🔗  Redes y enlaces de interés: https://moure.dev
👾  Discord: https://mouredev.com/discord
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
🕹  Twitch: https://twitch.tv/mouredev (directos de Lunes a Viernes)
🐦  Twitter: https://twitter.com/mouredev
📷  Instagram: https://instagram.com/mouredev
🎶  TikTok: https://tiktok.com/@mouredev
📩  Newsletter: http://newsletter.mouredev.com
👕  Merchandising: https://tienda.mouredev.com
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
🔔  SUSCRÍBETE Y ACTIVA LA CAMPANA: https://goo.gl/afPz3g
🏆  COLABORA CON EL CANAL: https://www.youtube.com/mouredevapps/join
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
💻  MI EQUIPO/SETUP:
https://mouredev.com/setup
https://www.amazon.es/shop/mouredev
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
🎓  CURSO COMPLETO iOS 15 y Swift 5.5  DESDE CERO:
https://www.udemy.com/course/swift_ios
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
⏳  TWITIMER, LA APP PARA APRENDER PROGRAMACIÓN DE LA COMUNIDAD:
https://twitimer.com
▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
⭐️  DESCUENTOS Y COLABORADORES:
• Elgato: https://e.lga.to/MoureDev
• Macnificos: https://macnificos.com/tienda/?tt=31560_12_407642_&amp;r=%2F
• Hostinger: https://hostinger.com/mouredev (Cupón &quot;MOUREDEV&quot; descuento 7%)
• MacPaw: https://macpaw.audw.net/c/2550109/94160/1733
• ClickUp: https://clickup.com?fp_ref=brais66&amp;promo=MOUREDEV
• GitKraken: https://www.gitkraken.com/invite/cZWhJq1v
• NordVPN: https://nordvpn.org/mouredev
• CodelyTV Pro: https://codely.tv/pro/mouredev 

#Hacker #Ciberseguridad #HackerLive]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.79JygZ7DUqw</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/79JygZ7DUqw.m4a" length="158175987" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 18:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/79JygZ7DUqw/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>38</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by MoureDev by Brais Moure published on Wednesday, October  6 2021 at 19:00:03</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck - Summarized by the Author - Mark Manson</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck - Author’s Summary

This is the official summary of the mega-bestseller &#x27;The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck: A Counterintuitive Approach to Living a Good Life&#x27; by me, Mark Manson. See below for chapter time codes.

Intro: 00:00
Chapter 1: DON&#x27;T TRY 02:43
Chapter 2: HAPPINESS IS A PROBLEM 06:46 
Chapter 3: YOU ARE NOT SPECIAL 11:03
Chapter 4: THE VALUE OF SUFFERING 15:03
Chapter 5: YOU ARE ALWAYS CHOOSING 18:19
Chapter 6: YOU&#x27;RE WRONG ABOUT EVERYTHING (BUT SO AM I) 23:05
Chapter 7: FAILURE IS THE WAY FORWARD 27:31
Chapter 8: THE IMPORTANCE OF SAYING NO 30:33
Chapter 9: AND THEN YOU DIE... 33:41

Like. Share. Comment. Subscribe. You know the drill.

Everything is Fucked: A Book About Hope Official Summary here: https://youtu.be/fEk5dhbNU70

—

Sign up for my newsletter to receive three actionable pieces of advice each week that could change your life - free sign up here: http://bit.ly/3JRg3NX

If you are not already a member of my premium membership, get access to my courses and exclusive writing here: http://bit.ly/3LwHWfi

I am Mark Manson, 3x #1 NY Times bestselling author of:

The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck - https://mrk.mn/3svfxcu
Everything Is F*cked: A Book About Hope - https://mrk.mn/2RNxVAD

I share other types of content to make you a less awful human in these places:

https://instagram.com/markmanson/
https://twitter.com/IAmMarkManson
https://facebook.com/Markmansonnet/
https://linkedin.com/in/markmanson/
https://www.tiktok.com/@iammarkmanson

Thanks for watching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.lz8sUiXAnbs</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/lz8sUiXAnbs.m4a" length="36650639" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 10:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/lz8sUiXAnbs/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>39</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Mark Manson published on Thursday, March  4 2021 at 20:13:55</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 6 Habits Of HIGHLY EFFECTIVE People You Can Copy! (CHANGE EVERYTHING) | Brendon Burchard - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Build IRONCLAD discipline in this free workshop: https://bit.ly/3pMVl6J

On Today&#x27;s Episode: 

It’s easy to admire people that have reached extraordinary levels of success, it’s hard to imagine what it takes to get there. Passing off someone’s excellence and success as unattainable for ourselves is a b.s. and it’s not what we’re about at Impact Theory. 

Your beliefs are malleable and what you believe about yourself matters. How you decide to live your life and show today matters also and if you’re not happy with the way you show up or how you’re living your life then do something about it.

Brendon Burchard is one of the world’s leading high performance coaches that has impacted and trained millions of people globally. His online personal growth platform is dedicated to teaching people how to bring the joy, live with intention, love the life you live, and matter to yourself and others everyday because you show up to go all-in on whatever you decide.

You’ve heard what it takes to be successful, but very few people share how to get beyond passion and shoot for obsession to attain insane levels of success, but today we are, so let’s go.

SHOW NOTES:

0:00 | Introduction to Brendon Burchard
2:22 | Generate the Energy You Want
10:15 | Raise Necessity with Obsession
15:51 | These 2 Things BUILD Your Identity
26:33 | Build These Skills Achieve More
35:47 | Honor the Struggle to Win

QUOTES:

“If you’re not a fun person when you&#x27;re broke, you’re not going to be that much more fun when you’re rich.” [4:00]

“High performers are generating the energy, and that means the mental, emotional and physical energy, that they feel is necessary to serve with excellence in a certain situation.” [9:45]

“People don’t want to exude that much passion which becomes obsession because they’re fearful of their obsessions.” [12:36] 

“If no one thinks you’re crazy you’re not yet operating to the outer limits of your potential.” [13:43]

“Being obsessed about something that gives you no feedback is not scary, being obsessed about something, like trying to make an impact in the world you’re going to get feedback.” [14:39]

“If you want to win, your identity has to be tied into that thing in which you are trying to succeed at and give to, and that takes a lot of guts to ut yourself all in…” [18:32]

“This is who I’m going to be and I’m going to build into that, and it is necessary for me to become that person.” [26:22]

“High performers are consistently seeking clarity in ‘who do I want to be?’ [...] in every situation.” [31:15]

“I don’t want a friction free life, [...] The journey to greatness begins the moment that our deep desires for comfort and for ease are overpowered by our desires to connect and contribute.”  [40:08]

“Determine what the questions at the end of your life are going to be.” [42:49]

Follow Brendon Burchard:
Website: https://brendon.com/ 
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brendonburchard/ 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/brendonburchardfan 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/BrendonBurchard 
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/user/BrendonBurchard]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.Q-xVb3V_zqI</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/Q-xVb3V_zqI.m4a" length="43989194" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/Q-xVb3V_zqI/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>40</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Tuesday, August 30 2022 at 13:00:25</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEGATHREAT: Why AI Is So Dangerous &amp; How It Could Destroy Humanity | Mo Gawdat - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Listen to Impact Theory on Amazon Music: https://music.amazon.com/podcasts/9e0db1b9-b46c-4e50-a9c5-add34b0ffe00/impact-theory-with-tom-bilyeu?ref=dm_sh_nzgPULGEOD2WFqOCd38MsElYP

Restart Your Life in 7 Days: http://bit.ly/42KM8OR

After reading Mo Gawdat’s book, Scary Smart, I knew right away this conversation was a must. As I think about AI’s capabilities – the good, the bad and possibly terrifying, I realize how serious this moment is in history for humanity.

Mo Gawdat is the former chief business officer for Google X and has built a monumental career in the tech industry working with the biggest names to reshape and reimagine the world as we know it. From IBM to Microsoft, Mo has lived at the cutting edge of technology and has taken a strong stance that AI is a bigger threat to humanity than global warming.

The AI dilemma is reshaping our future whether you’re in favor of it or not. The question is, are we even close to being prepared for humanity’s collision with artificial intelligence?

Strap in for the ride, we’re diving headfirst into this conversation and uncovering the alarming truth about how vulnerable we actually are and what that means for the next decade ahead.

QUOTES:

“It really is about a point of no return. Where if we cross that point of no return we have very little chance to bring the genie back into the bottle.”

“There is no shutting down AI, there is no reversing it, there is no stopping development of it.”

“We’ve never created a nuclear weapon that can create nuclear weapons.”

“The growth on the next chip in your phone is going to be a million times more than the computer that put people on the moon.”

“When we ask computers to communicate, at first they communicate like we tell them, but if they&#x27;re intelligent enough, they&#x27;ll start to say, ‘that&#x27;s too slow.’”

“One of our better scenarios, believe it or not, is that AI ignores us altogether.”

“Technology today can influence one human at a time.”


Follow Mo Gawdat:
Website: https://www.mogawdat.com/ 
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCilMYYyoot7vhLn4Tinzmmg 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/mgawdat 
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/mo_gawdat/]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.itY6VWpdECc</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/itY6VWpdECc.m4a" length="173357430" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/itY6VWpdECc/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>41</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Tuesday, June 20 2023 at 13:00:27</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Waking Up At 3:30 am Everyday Will CHANGE YOUR LIFE (Try This For 7 Days!) | Tom Bilyeu - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Click here to download your FREE guide to 100x YOUR EFFICIENCY IN 10 EASY STEPS: https://bit.ly/3F8qOJL

Build IRONCLAD discipline in this FREE workshop: https://bit.ly/3RUnYux

On Today&#x27;s Episode:

Do you enjoy the snooze alarm game? A lot of people you know including yourself do. It’s kind of fun but mostly torture. For 30 to 60 minutes, depending on your level of expertise, you get to see how many times you will hit the snooze button and sleep in 5 or 10 minute intervals before having to jump out of bed and mad dash through the morning to get ready. 

Every day, you wake up exhausted, you don’t get to the most important thing you told yourself the night before you would do first thing in the morning, your energy is low before noon and by 3 PM you’re begging yourself for a nap.

The key to breaking this cycle to start waking up at the time you want and need to is having the habits and routines built in place that make you so efficient that success becomes inevitable.

You don’t have to struggle every morning to get up early, you don’t need to set an alarm every night before bed to get up in the morning on time, and you don’t have to suffer through your days forever tired.

This is the video you need to hear to truly understand, how hardcore is hardcore for Tom Bilyeu when it comes to being the founder of a billion dollar company?

A few simple strategies you can start with right now are:

Go to bed same time (every day)
Do not use an alarm
Sleep as much as you need (it’s that important)

QUOTES:

“Your life will change forever the moment you decide to go to us early and really attack your day.”

“The snooze alarm says that you’ve not gotten control of your evenings.”

“You don’t need time to unwind, you are creating a torture cycle for yourself. You need a method for shutting your brain off.”

“I define truth as the thing that most efficiently moves you towards your goal.”

“My life is an exact reflection of my choices and that I made my day a little bit worst by not doing what I said I was going to do.”

“Boredom kills more dreams than failure I promise you.”

Follow Tom Bilyeu:
Website: https://impacttheory.com/ 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/TomBilyeu 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/tombilyeu]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.9RXdAdjy0_o</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/9RXdAdjy0_o.m4a" length="93113761" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/9RXdAdjy0_o/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>42</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Saturday, March 18 2023 at 13:00:06</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chat GPT, The FUTURE Of AI And Is It The End Of Human Civilization? | Tom Bilyeu - Tom Bilyeu</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Click here to download your FREE guide to 100x YOUR EFFICIENCY IN 10 EASY STEPS: https://bit.ly/3F8qOJL

Chat GPT AI went from 0 to over 100Million users in less than 2 months. AI is super fucking dangerous, but it’s inevitable, will make our lives better, and you should CAREFULLY love it. 

Is AI dangerous? Next to thermonuclear war and an asteroid strike, I’d say it’s the most radically dangerous threat that we face as a species. Buuuuut I’m still super excited. And by the end of this video you will be too.

If you’re terrified of AI right now, you’re rational. If you’re not at least worried it will take a wrong turn into James Cameron territory, you’re not paying attention. To paraphrase Elon Musk, the human endeavor to create AI could be the first step towards a technological utopia or a demon summoning circle. It’s not clear which way it will go. But one thing is for sure, we will not control it. And he’s right, but the truth is, the genie is out of the bottle, and we’re going to have to deal with it.  

For the most part our insatiable drive for progress is awesome. The modern world really is a miracle. We have buses that fly for the love of god. And if people like Eric Weinstein are correct, our thirst for progress will lead us to building technology that doesn’t just allow us to fly around the world, it will give us the ability to manipulate time and space itself - propelling us well beyond our solar system at faster than light speeds. 


I fear it will be a bit of both.

AI, which simply stands for Artificial Intelligence, is getting smart. Really smart. And AI doesn’t have to outsmart us by much to completely dominate us. Let me give you an example for scale: A moron is technically someone with an IQ of about 70. The average IQ in the US is 98. Einstein was estimated to be 160. And according to the Guiness book of World Records, the highest IQ ever recorded came in at a whopping 210. That means that a super genius is only 3 times smarter than a moron. But Einstein, who was actually only 2.3 times smarter than a moron, had insights that gave birth to nuclear power and nuclear bombs, not to mention lasers, GPS, and a whole lot more. Said another way, a little intelligence goes a loooooooong way. 

Nuclear warheads are scary enough, but AI isn’t going to be a little smarter than Einstein, it’s going to be a LOT smarter. Not 5 times smarter or 10 times or even 10,000 times smarter. We’re talking millions of times smarter. 

Despite the reality of all the bad stuff that’s coming, here are three traps we must avoid.
1. Burying our heads in the sand. 
2. Panicking. 
3. Trying to abolish AI.

Panicking is the same as actively taking your own intelligence offline. When you panic, blood leaves your prefrontal cortex, which is the seat of high level cognition. Therefore it actually makes you dumber. And in the face of artificial super intelligence that strikes me as a very bad idea. 

This is going to be the bleakest thing that I say today, but if we’re going to walk a wise path forward, we’ve got to face all of this. And, as they say, it’s darkest right before dawn, which I promise is coming. But first, here’s the reality you will instantly know to be true - when humans find powerful things we use them. 

Because AI as a weapon is a zero sum game. If only one nation develops it, it will be winner take all. And no one can risk an adversary getting Artificial Super Intelligence while they sit around entering funny prompts into ChatGPT. 

In the short term you need to do three things:

1. Reframe your thinking around AI. Don’t see it as the enemy. See it as a tool. You’re not going to be replaced by AI, at least not yet. You’re going to be replaced by a human using AI. Be the human that replaces others.
2. Figure out how AI is going to disrupt you. Face it head on. Don’t run. Don’t hide. Identify your vulnerabilities and shore up your skill set.
3. Identify all of the AI tools that are relevant to you and master them. Learn absolutely everything you can.

Remember, this is the very beginning of a very aggressive revolution. Moving quickly gives you advantages.

First of all, let me acknowledge that I’m a pundit here, not an expert. While we’re working feverishly to integrate AI into our company’s workflow, I’m not the guy who can tell you how AI works under the hood. So what follows will be me thinking out loud based on what I’ve learned from the experts in my attempts to use AI in both my daily life and the daily operations of my company.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.F2LeyULGF2Q</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/F2LeyULGF2Q.m4a" length="16948387" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/F2LeyULGF2Q/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>43</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Tom Bilyeu published on Wednesday, March 15 2023 at 23:13:01</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIEMPOS DECISIVOS: EL FINAL DEL PRINCIPIO - Vlog de Marc Vidal - Marc Vidal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[La historia del dinero, sus usos y sus bancos. Te explico la situación actual y te dejo dos intervenciones en televisión. Ha empezado la fase final del principio. A partir de ahora se desarrollará todo. Esta es la situación actual en la que nos encontramos, sin un patrón establecido y con sistemas monetarios que varían de un país a otro. Y ahora, han decidido emitir CDBCs para que no puedas quejarte.  Como te digo, os dejo con dos vídeos de esta semana. Uno en Horizonte y otro en El Cascabel. De los pocos sitios que me permiten ir. Ya sabes… Espero que os guste. Seguiré subiendo material como pueda aunque me voy unos días con la familia a descansar en esta semana santa. Leed mucho, descansad y comed bien. Nos vemos pronto, os dejo con estas dos intervenciones]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.Of5d57GLAiY</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/Of5d57GLAiY.m4a" length="30397215" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 17:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/Of5d57GLAiY/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>44</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Marc Vidal published on Saturday, April  1 2023 at 19:21:17</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Técnicas para hablar fluido y claro - Teresa Baró • Comunicación de éxito</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Cuando hablas, ¿la gente se queda con la boca abierta o se aburre? Si es lo segundo, prepárate para tomar nota de las mejores técnicas y aprende cómo hablar de forma fluida, sin esfuerzo y sin aburrir a los demás. 

Fórmate con mis cursos 👉 https://bit.ly/TBcursos

🔽 También te puede interesar 🔽
Cómo usar la voz para influir y persuadir https://youtu.be/C2Hr99q2JBI
Los 3 pilares para hablar en público y disfrutar https://youtu.be/Lt05kaqHa08
De qué hablar cuando no sabemos de qué hablar https://youtu.be/W2ATY235XIQ
No cometas estos errores en una conversación https://youtu.be/twX49imskpI

👀 Mi libro &quot;La Gran Guía del lenguaje no verbal&quot; 👉 https://amzn.to/3fyxF2e

✔ Si eres mujer y quieres dar un gran salto en tu carrera, únete a la FÓRMULA IMPARABLE 👉 
https://www.teresabaro.com/es/formula_imparable/

📕  Mis libros https://www.teresabaro.com/mis-libros/

▶ Me puedes encontrar por mis redes sociales:
Twitter: https://twitter.com/tbarocatafau
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/tbarocatafau/
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/teresabarocom/ 
Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/teresa-baro-comunicacion-no-verbal/

▶ Conoce más sobre mi en: https://www.teresabaro.com/
▶ Descubre mis cursos: https://www.teresabaro.com/es/formate/]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.U2lWFRFwZLE</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/U2lWFRFwZLE.m4a" length="8771288" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 18:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/U2lWFRFwZLE/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>45</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Teresa Baró • Comunicación de éxito published on Thursday, July  7 2022 at 18:00:08</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Way To Launch Your Startup | Startup School - Y Combinator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Kat Mañalac is the head of YC&#x27;s Outreach team and advises early stage founders on their launches during the YC batch. She shares the multitude of ways to launch a product and how to get attention for them. Her talk provides tangible strategies and examples of startup launches and will change the way you think about launching.

Apply to Y Combinator: https://www.ycombinator.com/apply/
Work at a startup: https://www.ycombinator.com/jobs

Chapters (Powered by https://bit.ly/chapterme-yc) - 
00:00 - Launching Your Startup
01:28 - When Should I Launch My Startup?
03:42 - One Sentence Pitch
05:19 - How to Create a Short Memorable Description
09:17 - When is the X for Y Construction Not Too Cliche?
12:05 - Types of Launches
20:43 - Summary]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.u36A-YTxiOw</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/u36A-YTxiOw.m4a" length="20513048" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 17:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/u36A-YTxiOw/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>46</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Y Combinator published on Thursday, February  9 2023 at 22:44:27</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build An MVP | Startup School - Y Combinator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Y Combinator Group Partner, Michael Seibel, explains how to build a minimum viable product (MVP) for your startup idea. Using examples from real YC companies, Michael walks through how to determine your MVP feature set, build prototypes and demos for user testing, and present your MVP to early customers or investors.

Apply to Y Combinator: https://www.ycombinator.com/apply/ 
Work at a startup: https://www.ycombinator.com/jobs

Chapters (Powered by https://bit.ly/chapterme-yc) - 
00:00 - How to Build an Minimum Viable Product (MVP)?
01:50 - Pre-launch Startup Goals
04:26 - Founders Biggest Fear
07:17 - Examples - Software MVP
07:48 - Airbnb
08:36 - Twitch
09:15 - Stripe
10:36 - Solving Hair On Fire Problem
14:12 - Build an MVP Quickly
15:51 - Outro]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.QRZ_l7cVzzU</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/QRZ_l7cVzzU.m4a" length="16389640" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 17:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/QRZ_l7cVzzU/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>47</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Y Combinator published on Wednesday, March 15 2023 at 19:01:04</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuroscientist: This Simple Skill Will Make You More Powerful In Life | Andrew Huberman - Diy Things</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Neuroscientist: This Simple Skill Will Make You More Powerful In Life | Andrew Huberman

Also, in this video Neuroscientist - Andrew Huberman explains the 5 things in life which cannot be replaced.

Neuroscientist: There&#x27;s NO replacement for these 5 Things | Andrew Huberman. 2023

Neuroscientist Dr. Andrew Huberman shares his insights on the five habits that have no replacement when it comes to maintaining good health and well-being. He emphasizes the importance of getting enough sleep, regular exercise, a balanced and nutritious diet, socializing with others, and staying hydrated. 

 #andrewhuberman #huberman  #speech  #advice #motivation]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.g55rPgT4bj4</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/g55rPgT4bj4.m4a" length="6837098" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/g55rPgT4bj4/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>48</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Diy Things published on Monday, February  6 2023 at 20:25:23</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Steve Jobs Heres To The Crazy Ones - Nathan Hulls</title>
      <description><![CDATA[http://www.NathanHulls.com

Steve Jobs narrates the first of Apples &#x27;Think Different&#x27; commercial &quot;Here&#x27;s to the Crazy Ones&quot;. It never aired. Richard Dreyfuss did the voice over for the original spot that aired.

&quot;The ones who are crazy enough to think that they can change the world, are the ones who do&quot;

http://www.nathanhulls.com]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.-z4NS2zdrZc</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/-z4NS2zdrZc.m4a" length="989115" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 23:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/-z4NS2zdrZc/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>49</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Nathan Hulls published on Wednesday, September 26 2012 at 03:42:01</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In The Night Garden Theme | Intro | Music | Titles - Cbeebies - High Quality - waybuloouk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[This is the intro to the popular pre school tv series In The Night Garden. Iggle Piggle, Upsy Daisy, Makka Pakka. 

Check out this Amazon In The Night Garden shop, delivery on orders over £5 are free: http://astore.amazon.co.uk/night-garden-toys-21

Or these other Amazon shops:
http://astore.amazon.co.uk/timmy-time-21
http://astore.amazon.co.uk/waybuloo-shop-21
http://astore.amazon.co.uk/pig-peppa-21
http://astore.amazon.co.uk/leapster-21]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.NQ5ku4z1pjs</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/NQ5ku4z1pjs.m4a" length="1980711" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 23:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/NQ5ku4z1pjs/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>50</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by waybuloouk published on Saturday, September 26 2009 at 17:55:07</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 ONE-MINUTE Habits That Save Me 20+ Hours a Week - Time Management For Busy People - Liam Porritt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The first 100 people to download Endel will get a free week of audio experiences - https://app.adjust.com/b8wxub6?campaign=liamporritt_January2023&amp;adgroup=youtube

In our busy lives, a few hours a week means time for a date, or a few hours of self-love pruning in the bath - so imagine what you could do with 10, 20 or even more extra time each week 🤯 

Well, from reading some of the best time management books out there, these are my top 4 quick habits to efficiently manage your time, which save me hours each week 🙌 They are simple, but hugely effective techniques to make the most of our 16 or so waking hours a day, and honestly are some of the core techniques that allow me to keep up a demanding career as a corporate lawyer, while running multiple businesses on the side 👨‍💻

The key to these habits is (as with all habits) consistency… kinda obvious, I know. But with these habits especially, they really don’t take much effort, but they do require a consistent consciousness of how you are working. So, try to keep each of these in mind as you get ready for, and then during, each of your work sessions 🫶

00:00 How I Juggle Everything
00:28 Cinema Mode
02:12 Batch By Project &amp; Task
06:27 Avoid Work
07:42 Multitask

………………………………………………….

Menos - Minimalist, sustainable design (by Liam &amp; Beth)

Sign up to get pre-launch access to one of only 200 grey and 400 black Menos backpack, made from recycled plastic - https://wearemenos.com ✨ 

Beth and I have created Menos to bring minimalist, sustainable design to help us all boss the everyday. Follow Menos (@wearemenos on Instagram) - https://instagram.com/wearemenos 

………………………………………………….

Get The Done App &amp; Other Productivity Apps - Completely Free For A Whole Year!

https://growthbundle.com/referral/?referrer=Liam&amp;referral-code=liamporritt&amp;source=partner

………………………………………………….

My Free Trello Masterclass

&#x27;More Focus, Less Stress - Build Your Ultimate Productivity System in Trello&#x27; is my FREE course (Trello is also FREE), which you can take by signing up for a free 2-week SkillShare trial: https://skl.sh/3h2XpV1

... The course walks you through how to build your customised version of my insanely powerful (but simple) Trello productivity system (aka the app that keeps me focused for 10 hours per day!) 📱

………………………………………………….

About Me

I&#x27;m a lawyer, part-time YouTuber, son, brother, startup founder, fiancé, black coffee drinker and plant dad. I graduated from Cambridge University (where I studied French and Spanish), topped my law school class and now work for a corporate law firm in London as a trainee solicitor (which takes up a lot of my time)!

Around that, I&#x27;m a big fan of discovering new ways of thinking, of balancing work with life, and of performing to the very best of my ability. Ohh, and being happy. And I try to share all that on this YouTube channel 😀

Fun fact: I believe we massively overplay the role of “natural talent” 😮 AND… I also believe that TOGETHER, WE ARE ALL CAPABLE OF POSITIVITY, PRODUCTIVITY AND SUCCESS.

📸  Instagram – https://www.instagram.com/liam.porritt/
🌍  My little kingdom – https://liamporritt.com

………………………………………………….

Thanks so much to Endel for sponsoring this video 😀]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">com.uuebcast.uuid.R5i8alK5hPo</guid>
      <enclosure url="http://lab.oliverbarreto.com/static/media/R5i8alK5hPo.m4a" length="8899080" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 23:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <itunes:image href="http://i.ytimg.com/vi/R5i8alK5hPo/hqdefault.jpg"/>
      <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:order>51</itunes:order>
      <itunes:subtitle>by Liam Porritt published on Tuesday, January 24 2023 at 16:00:21</itunes:subtitle>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
